<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" >
<channel>
        <title>Eurogamer.net</title>
        <description>Bad puns and video games since 1999.</description>
        <link>https://www.eurogamer.net/</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:15:08 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<ttl>5</ttl>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:15:08 +0100</pubDate>
        	<item>
		<title>Square Enix insists it will not release Final Fantasy 7 Remake digital version early</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-04-11-13/square-enix-says-it-will-not-release-final-fantasy-7-remake-digital-version-early-1585995220423.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089379.jpg" alt=""/><p>Square Enix has insisted it will not release the digital version of Final Fantasy 7 Remake early - despite the fact physical copies are on-sale now.</p><p>Physical copies of the hotly anticipated remake are out in the wild ahead of the official 10th April 2020 release date after <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-28-final-fantasy-7-remake-street-date-broken-as-square-enix-issues-release-date-warning">Square Enix deliberately shipped them early</a> in Europe and Australia amid the ongoing disruption caused by the coronavirus to ensure they reached fans by release date.</p><p>This has caused a great deal of frustration for those who intend to download the game rather than buy on-disc, or those who have already pre-ordered via the PlayStation Store.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-square-enix-says-it-will-not-release-final-fantasy-7-remake-digital-version-early">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-square-enix-says-it-will-not-release-final-fantasy-7-remake-digital-version-early</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089379</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:13:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rocksmith DLC comes to an end as dev moves on to new project</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-04-10-17/rocksmith-dlc-comes-to-an-end-as-dev-moves-on-to-new-project-1585991858568.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089375.jpg" alt=""/><p>The developer of Rocksmith has moved into a new project.</p><p>DLC for Ubisoft's guitar-teaching game has now come to an end, Ubisoft San Francisco announced in a <a href="https://rocksmith.ubisoft.com/rocksmith/en-us/news/152-361505-16/the-future-of-rocksmith" target="_blank">blog post</a>.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2012-11-08-rocksmith-review">Rocksmith</a>, which lets you plug in pretty much any electric guitar and play, launched in October 2011 for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360, with a PC release in 2012. A sequel, dubbed <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2013-12-13-rocksmith-2014-edition-review">Rocksmith 2014</a>, came out in 2013. Our Ian Higton had a strum on that, which you can see in the video below.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-rocksmith-dlc-comes-to-an-end-as-dev-moves-on-to-new-project">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-rocksmith-dlc-comes-to-an-end-as-dev-moves-on-to-new-project</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089375</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 10:19:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Saints Row: The Third Remastered outed by rating board</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-04-09-52/saints-row-the-third-remastered-outed-by-rating-board-1585990351989.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089372.jpg" alt=""/><p>It looks like a remaster of Saints Row: The Third is coming soon.</p><p>The Entertainment Software Rating Board (ESRB) has a <a href="https://www.esrb.org/ratings/36794/Saints+Row%3A+The+Third+Remastered/" target="_blank">listing</a> for Saints Row: The Third Remastered, courtesy of publisher Koch Media and due out on PC, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One.</p><p>Volition's Saints Row: The Third launched back in 2011 for PC, PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 by now-defunct publisher THQ. The outlandish Grand Theft Auto-style game was infamous for its sex toy bat, which was an in-game weapon as well as an actual real-life promotional tool. A Nintendo Switch port, which wasn't great according to <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2019-saints-row-the-third-switch-analysis">Digital Foundry</a>, came out in 2019.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-saints-row-the-third-remastered-outed-by-rating-board">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-saints-row-the-third-remastered-outed-by-rating-board</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089372</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 09:53:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The pleasures of a game world you look down upon</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-13-24/-1585916643402.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089262.jpg" alt=""/><p>It's a famous story, <a href="https://www.futilitycloset.com/2017/07/20/lost-treasure/" target="_blank">but a good one.</a> When Robert Louis Stevenson was writing Treasure Island, he started out by drawing a map - a map of the island itself. One of his biographers - I think it was Claire Harman, and if you walk away from this piece with anything it should be a desire to read her perceptive and generous book on Stevenson - has pointed out that the map looks a bit like Scotland. Anyway, he drew the map and then he wrote the book, at times the map actually guiding the narrative. The land was sacred and the words had to fit it. Stevenson!</p><p>Then he sent the map to his publisher and it was lost in the post. He had to draw another version, returning to the text and pulling the map back out of the book. He did a good enough job, clearly  - the rest of us have only ever seen his copy. But still: "Somehow it was never Treasure Island to me."</p><p>I think about this story almost every day at the moment, and not only because I am permanently dizzy for Stevenson. It's because every day I log into Animal Crossing and I walk around and I do the weeding - Stevenson loved weeding, incidentally, and wrote about weeds thrillingly - and I pop balloons and I find Gulliver's phone parts for him and send him on his way. And all the time Animal Crossing reminds me of Treasure Island. I like to play with the camera set high above me and looking down on everything. This is the classic Animal Crossing view, and as much as I like the rolling drum perspective of the later games that allows you to see the sky above and the stars at night, it still feels like the right way to play. All around me the landscape is basically a map. Like Stevenson I find something truly energising about looking down on the terrain. I love games that have this perspective: top-down games!</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-the-pleasures-of-a-game-world-you-look-down-upon">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-04-the-pleasures-of-a-game-world-you-look-down-upon</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089262</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Here's a look at Elite Dangerous' long-awaited Fleet Carriers</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-04-00-54/heres-a-look-at-elite-dangerous-long-awaited-fleet-carriers-1585958050375.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089359.jpg" alt=""/><p>Elite Dangerous has been dangling the tantalising space carrot of 16-person Fleet Carriers for three years now, but finally, following a succession of lengthy delays, they're almost here - and developer Frontier has offered a closer look in a brand-new livestream and trailer.</p><p>Fleet Carriers, which were initially planned for <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2017-10-10-elite-dangerous-future-is-bright-and-a-little-less-beige">2018's Beyond update</a>, are described as "mobile starships and trading hubs capable of transporting multiple allies", and can accommodate up to 16 players, thanks to their eight large, four medium, and four small landing pads.</p><p>While they have the potential to be a bustling hive of social activity for multiple space pals, Fleet Carriers are owned and piloted by a single Commander - one who'll need to cough up 5,000,000,000 credits for the privilege of owning the basic model, although that does include a Commodity Market and a Tritium Depot for the price.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-heres-a-look-at-elite-dangerous-long-awaited-fleet-carriers">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-heres-a-look-at-elite-dangerous-long-awaited-fleet-carriers</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089359</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 23:45:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Stardew-Valley-inspired magic school sim Witchbrook gets a gorgeous new look</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-21-26/chucklefishs-stardew-valley-inspired-magic-academy-sim-witchbrook-gets-a-gorgeous-new-look-1585945581795.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089343.jpg" alt=""/><p>Developer Chucklefish has shared a fresh batch of screenshots for its Stardew-Valley-inspired wizarding-school-meets-village-life sim Witchbrook, and it's all change on the visual front since its last public outing - with its revamped art style looking very lovely indeed.</p><p>Witchbrook first reared its head back in 2017, its <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2017-09-13-stardew-valley-publisher-reveals-new-details-on-magic-school-rpg">informal reveal</a> consisting of a handful of screenshots and a very loose outline of its wizarding theme - it didn't even have a title at that point. A few months later, Chucklefish <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2017-10-03-chucklefish-conjures-up-new-details-on-its-mysterious-magic-school-sim">shared more of its ideas</a> for the experience - including schooling, magic, crafting, potion making, romance, and farming, even a splash of Zelda-inspired combat - and then, finally, in 2018, it got its name.</p><p>Through all of that, Witchbrook's early screenshots sported an appealingly bold pixel-art aesthetic, whose top-down perspective, clean lines, and colour palette had a touch of Earthbound and classic Pokemon about them. Now though, a fresh crop of images have emerged <a href="https://www.witchbrook.com">on Witchbrook's website</a>, and the dramatic shift in art style has turned an already attractive game into an absolutely gorgeous one.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-stardew-valley-inspired-magic-school-sim-witchbrook-gets-a-gorgeous-new-look">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-stardew-valley-inspired-magic-school-sim-witchbrook-gets-a-gorgeous-new-look</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089343</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 20:53:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Monster Boy dev shows off the DuckTales game it pitched to Disney</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-22-39/wonder-boy-and-the-cursed-kingdom-dev-show-off-the-ducktales-game-that-might-have-been-1585949971798.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089340.jpg" alt=""/><p>Game Atelier, the developer behind <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2018-12-11-monster-boy-and-the-cursed-kingdom-review-a-vital-updating-of-a-classic-series">2018's sublime platformer</a> Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom, has offered a glimpse of DuckTales QuackShots, a gorgeous hand-drawn take on Disney's beloved cartoon caper which sadly - curse the video game gods - just wasn't to be, never making it past the pitching stage.</p><p>QuackShots first reared its head <a href="https://twitter.com/FDG_Games/status/1245266966790705152?s=20">earlier this week</a> when Cursed Kingdom publisher FDG Entertainment announced it as its next project and latest collaboration with Game Atelier. Unfortunately, the announcement just so happened to land on 1st April, leaving onlookers as suspicious as they were excited by the news - skepticism that proved merited when FDG owned up to its April Fool's japery the following day.</p><p>Although hardly unexpected, the truth was still a bit of a disappointment; after all, not only does DuckTales - both the cartoon series and its various game adaptations, starting with Capcom's 8-bit classic - have a legion of admirers eager to see Scrooge McDuck and friends get the modern day video game treatment, the prospect of Game Atelier taking the reins on the project following its sterling Wonder Boy revival was a genuinely exciting one.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-monster-boy-dev-shows-off-the-ducktales-game-it-pitched-to-disney">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-monster-boy-dev-shows-off-the-ducktales-game-it-pitched-to-disney</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089340</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 19:29:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Gone Home and Hob are currently free on the Epic Games Store</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-17-52/gone-home-and-hob-are-currently-free-on-the-epic-games-store-1585932777367.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089319.jpg" alt=""/><p>Given that your daily doses of shameless outdoor cavorting are likely fairly regulated right now, you probably won't object to more free stuff being bundled into your laps to keep those hours distractedly ticking by - and Epic Games is once again on hand to do just that, this time flinging Gone Home and Hob up onto its store's weekly freebie table.</p><p>Gone Home, of course, needs little introduction, having brought the so-called walking simulator genre crashing into the limelight back in 2013. Developed by The Fullbright Company, it tells the story of a young woman who returns to her family home after a year abroad, only to find it mysteriously deserted.</p><p>What follows is a frequently captivating, wonderfully authentic family drama that slowly unfolds as players piece together the clues and scraps of information strewn naturally around the expansive home. It's a little bit spooky, surprisingly moving, and should even managed to prod a few nostalgia buttons, given its keenly realised 90s setting.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-gone-home-and-hob-are-currently-free-on-the-epic-games-store">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-gone-home-and-hob-are-currently-free-on-the-epic-games-store</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089319</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 17:27:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rust revamps farming system, adds horse poop</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-14-34/-1585920876300.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089281.jpg" alt=""/><p>Time to really get serious about growing that hemp for... clothing, as Rust has introduced a new update, and it's all about farming. </p><p>The rework focuses on giving players a more in-depth system for farming, in which "all conditions of a plant are now important" - with better conditions giving better rewards. For the best yields, you'll need to get the lighting, water saturation, ground condition and temperature of your plants right. </p><p>Thankfully, there's an info panel to help with all that, which shows you real-time progress on conditions as you change them, along with the plant's requirements. "Each plant type can have different resiliences to the various conditions, meaning some will grow more easily in certain areas than others," explains the <a href="https://rust.facepunch.com/blog/farming-update">blog post</a>. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-rust-revamps-farming-system-adds-poop">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-rust-revamps-farming-system-adds-poop</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089281</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:14:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>There's something rotten about Animal Crossing's egg event</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-15-02/theres-something-rotten-about-animal-crossings-egg-event-1585922559361.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089272.jpg" alt=""/><p>Let's be clear, for the first week and a bit of Animal Crossing: New Horizons, Nintendo played an absolute blinder. The introduction is a masterful ramp up to the traditional Animal Crossing experience, functionality and character building day over day until you reach a point you realise you've been playing a prologue all this time. The game proper is now ready to unfold. The whole experience is now wide open. You have toiled and crafted and you are ready for... eggs? </p><p>Eggs. The eggs are everywhere. And they stink. </p><p>Now, I think there's an element of bad timing here - albeit one Nintendo is still in charge of. When April rolled around, most people who had got the game on day one were now just settling into their island life proper. March's end was a gentle rush to gain stringfish and sturgeon before the season changed, but players had found their daily Animal Crossing rhythms. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-theres-something-rotten-about-animal-crossings-egg-event">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-theres-something-rotten-about-animal-crossings-egg-event</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089272</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 14:52:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Modern Warfare 2 Remastered: a campaign classic transitions beautifully to PS4</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-12-41/digitalfoundry-2020-modern-warfare-2-remastered-tech-analysis-1585914099121.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089252.jpg" alt=""/><p>Who knew that a Call of Duty campaign that released in 2009 would hold up so well today? Remastered, remade, revamped - developer Beenox delivers an excellent current-gen rendition of one of the all-time great Call of Duty campaigns. With this new rendition of Modern Warfare 2, we get vastly improved modelling and art along with remade cutscenes with new motion capture. On top of a revamped post-process pipeline and HDR support, it's an experience that still holds up today.</p><p>It's not quite the complete package, though. Unlike the original Modern Warfare Remastered, this is just the single-player campaign - multiplayer is completely excised from the product. It was a huge part of the game that will be sorely missed; faster, more chaotic than the original - with heartbeat sensors, more elaborate perks and killstreak rewards that escalated to tactical nukes. Even though we do have the 2019 reboot adding classic maps from older games to the rotation, it would have been nice to have.</p><p>On top of that, despite being a multi-platform development, it is a timed exclusive for PlayStation 4 owners - in the here and now, at least. Xbox One and PC versions will arrive further on down the line, and I'm certainly intrigued to see how Beenox tackles the Microsoft platform: the original Modern Warfare Remastered never received full-blooded support for Xbox One X. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-modern-warfare-2-remastered-tech-analysis">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-modern-warfare-2-remastered-tech-analysis</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089252</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 14:31:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Five of the Best: Title screens</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-12-26/five-of-the-best-title-screens-1585913214210.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089202.jpg" alt=""/><p><em>Five of the Best is a weekly series about the bits of games we overlook. I'm talking about potions, hubs, bags, mountains, anything really - but things we ignore at the time. Then, years later, we find they're cemented in our memory, inseparable from our experience of the game. Turns out they were important after all. So now we're celebrating them.</em></p><p><em>Five of the Best works like this. Various Eurogamer writers will share their memories in the article and then you - probably outraged we didn't include the thing you're thinking of - can share the thing you're thinking of in the comments below. We've had some great discussions in <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/archive/five-of-the-best">our other Five of the Best pieces</a>. Some of you have memories like elephants!</em></p><p><em>Today's Five of the Best...</em></p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-five-of-the-best-title-screens">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-five-of-the-best-title-screens</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089202</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Animal Crossing Grandma reacts to character named after her in New Horizons</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-11-46/animal-crossing-grandma-reacts-to-character-named-after-her-in-new-horizons-1585910812651.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089239.jpg" alt=""/><p>If you think you've already put a fair few hours into Animal Crossing: New Horizons, you probably still have some work to do before you reach the levels achieved by 88-year-old Audrey in New Leaf. Last year she became an internet sensation after her grandson, developer Paul Hubans, shared an image of her 3580 hours of play time (a number which has likely only increased since then). More recently players noticed <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-17-animal-crossing-grandma-has-a-character-named-after-her-in-new-horizons">she had a character named after her in New Horizons called Audie</a> - and now, we finally have a chance to see her reaction. </p><p>In a video made by Hubans, Audrey said she "didn't know" for sure if the character was named after her, but agreed it was likely as Audie was the name of her New Leaf mayor. All in all, it seems she felt pretty good about it. "I wanted to tell your mother but I couldn't get her to stay on the phone," she said in response to a question from her grandson.  </p><p>After players first spotted screenshots of Audie, I asked Hubans about Audrey's reaction to hearing the news, who told me she "seemed pretty amused about it but confused as to why they made her a wolf. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-animal-crossing-grandma-reacts-to-character-named-after-her-in-new-horizons">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-animal-crossing-grandma-reacts-to-character-named-after-her-in-new-horizons</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089239</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 11:55:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Platinum Games plots fifth reveal after April Fool's fourth falls flat</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-11-42/-1585910534295.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089237.jpg" alt=""/><p>Bayonetta and The Wonderful 101 developer Platinum Games has reassured fans left disappointed by yesterday's April Fools joke that it still has one announcement left in the bag. </p><p>Back in early February, Platinum promised four big reveals for the coming weeks, beginning with its <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-02-03-wonderful-101-remastered-smashes-kickstarter-goal-in-less-than-four-hours">The Wonderful 101: Remastered port</a>. </p><p>Later that month, the second surprise was revealed as Platinum mastermind Hideki Kamiya's next new game, <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-02-26-platinum-games-kamiya-announces-mysterious-project-g-g">the mysterious Project GG</a>. And a day later, the third announcement turned out to be a whole new studio, Platinum Games Tokyo, which would explore live game projects.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-platinum-games-plots-fifth-reveal-after-april-fools-fourth-falls-flat">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-platinum-games-plots-fifth-reveal-after-april-fools-fourth-falls-flat</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089237</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 11:48:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare multiplayer free for the weekend</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-11-05/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-multiplayer-free-for-the-weekend-1585908347855.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089229.jpg" alt=""/><p>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare's multiplayer is free to play this weekend.</p><p>You can get free access to multiplayer through the free-to-download battle royale, Warzone, all weekend long. Specifically, the promotion goes live at 6pm UK time tonight, 3rd April, and ends at 6pm UK time on 6th April.</p><p>Here's how it works: in the Warzone lobby, you'll see the Stocked Up, Locked Down 24/7 playlist. This playlist features two maps: Atlas Superstore (10v10), and Shoot House (6v6) - two of the better Modern Warfare multiplayer maps. Game modes include Team Deathmatch, Domination and Hardpoint.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-multiplayer-free-for-the-weekend">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-multiplayer-free-for-the-weekend</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089229</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Double-A Team: Sleeping Dogs lies on both sides of the law</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-16-05/the-double-a-team-sleeping-dogs-lies-on-both-sides-of-the-law-1585839912246.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089091.jpg" alt=""/><p>Sleeping Dogs isn't the most original game out there. It's open-world, released at the height of Assassin's Creed's popularity and the year before GTA 5. You play as Wei Shen, a Chinese-American cop who must go undercover in the Triads. The only catch is that many of Shen's friends and even family are Triad members, and he must - dun dun dun - choose which side of the law his loyalty lies on.</p><p>Like I said, not the most original. The Departed (itself based upon a Hong Kong cop saga in Internal Affairs) is the best modern example of the undercover cop story, but it's a narrative that goes back beyond 1949's White Heat, bypassing Reservoir Dogs, Prince Of The City and even White Chicks, which as we all know is White Heat's long-awaited sequel. It might not have anything particularly unique at its core then, but it nails one aspect of its story to the floorboards, in a way that many games since have tried and mostly failed to replicate: duality.</p><p>Morality and choice in games is very in vogue right now. Perhaps it's because, burdened by student loans, long hours for minimal pay and a skyrocketing divide between the haves and the have-nots, our real lives often seem devoid of choices. Maybe it's because social media makes us all so angry that there are so many bastard-coated-bastards out there and we're so desensitized to shooter violence that being bad just feels so cathartically good. Maybe it's just fun. Maybe it's Maybelline.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-the-double-a-team-sleeping-dogs-lies-on-both-sides-of-the-law">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-the-double-a-team-sleeping-dogs-lies-on-both-sides-of-the-law</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089091</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Outer Wilds scoops BAFTA's Best Game award</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-10-52/-1585907547373.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089223.jpg" alt=""/><p>Outer Wilds and Disco Elysium were the big winners at last night's BAFTA Games Awards, which was presented from home by host Dara O'Briain.</p><p>The unusual format of this year's ceremony also required all nominees to submit an acceptance video in case they won, which let us see Disco Elysium team members thanking BAFTA while hanging out with their sheep.</p><p>Outer Wilds won several of the night's biggest awards: Best Game, Game Design and Original Property. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-outer-wilds-scoops-baftas-best-game-award">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-outer-wilds-scoops-baftas-best-game-award</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089223</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 10:56:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord is janky as hell, but I absolutely love it</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-10-05/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-is-janky-as-hell-but-i-absolutely-love-it-1585904756369.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089193.jpg" alt=""/><p>Honestly, you wait the best part of a decade for some of your favourite franchises to come back and then two of them arrive in the same month. Typical, isn't it?</p><p>Not only did March see a new Half-Life game from Valve, but for some of us there was an equally big surprise: the honest to God release of Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord. Well, not quite the full release, it's in Early Access for the time being, but for those of us that have been following its development for <em>eight</em> years now, we'll take it. We'll absolutely take it.</p><p>Now, as you might have seen already, <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-you-could-briefly-play-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-as-an-actual-baby-and-it-was-hilarious">I did find myself briefly sidetracked by a now-patched bug that allowed me to ride around the world of Calradia as an actual baby</a>, slaying bandits and ne'er-do-wells as I went. But aside from that I've also managed to clock up nearly 20 hours with Mount and Blade 2, and there's a lot to take in.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-is-janky-as-hell-but-i-absolutely-love-it">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-is-janky-as-hell-but-i-absolutely-love-it</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089193</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lost Words: Beyond the Page review - a simple, flawed yet beautiful adventure</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-16-22/lost-words-beyond-the-page-review-1585840941774.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089047.jpg" alt=""/><p>Scrambling over Izzy's words - literally; that's how we traverse here - I realise I don't want to carry on. My avatar - a small, faceless girl with dark, flowing hair who pirouettes onto each word with the grace and elegance of the ballerina I never could be - stands still as my fingers sit motionless on my controller. There's a little tear on the opposite side that signals it's time to turn the page, but I can't. I'm stuck. Not because I can't move, but because I don't want to. I know how this is going to end - we all know how this story ends.</p><p>It's been some time since I was the age of our protagonist. Like Izzy, I dreamed of being a writer and kept a journal through my formative years, vomiting my thoughts and desires and teenage angst onto the page in curly adolescent script. Like Izzy - like all of us - I've lost people I loved and didn't know how to endure the devastation it caused, nor the white-hot rage and howling emptiness that followed. </p><p>Knowing it was coming didn't even soften the blow, by the way. Lost Words: Beyond the Page gut-punched me in a way I didn't quite expect. It'd lulled me into a false sense of security, disguising itself as a simple, if beautiful, 2D platformer that marries two disparate games that, if I'm honest, lack a little challenge and sophistication. There are no hyper-real graphics or intricate animations here. No complex puzzling or dexterous platforming. Just a poignant tale of love and loss tangled up in a make-believe world.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-lost-words-beyond-the-page-review">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-03-lost-words-beyond-the-page-review</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089047</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:15:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Darkest Dungeon is getting an arena-based PvP mode in its new Butcher's Circus DLC</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-03-00-45/darkest-dungeon-pvp-dlc-coming-in-may-1585871102077.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089167.jpg" alt=""/><p>Developer Red Hook Studios' brilliant but punishing Lovecraft-inspired strategy RPG, Darkest Dungeon, is getting a brand-new chunk of DLC next month. It's called The Butcher's Circus and, rather unexpectedly, adds PvP arena battles to the previously single-player game.</p><p>Up until now, Darkest Dungeon, which initially launched in 2016, has remained a staunchly solo pursuit, tasking players with delving ever-deeper into the antediluvian corners of an ancient hamlet and its surrounding environs - seeking treasure, avoiding traps, and battling cosmic horrors in time-honoured turn-based fashion.</p><p>Its unquestionable allure was found in the sheer thrill of besting its cliff-like difficulty curve, which delighted in sending party members to the brink of madness, imbuing them with (usually) negative quirks and making already tough challenges even harder - in turn forcing a stressfully satisfying balancing act between deeper exploration and hero preservation.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-darkest-dungeon-is-getting-an-arena-based-pvp-mode-in-its-new-butchers-circus-paid-dlc">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-darkest-dungeon-is-getting-an-arena-based-pvp-mode-in-its-new-butchers-circus-paid-dlc</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089167</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 23:40:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Acclaimed Castlevania-esque rogue-like platformer Rogue Legacy is getting a sequel</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-23-23/acclaimed-rogue-like-platformer-rogue-legacy-is-getting-a-sequel-1585866213022.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089164.jpg" alt=""/><p>Following an <a href="https://twitter.com/CellarDoorGames/status/1245473323032723458?s=20">April Fool's Day tease</a> that made its veracity uncertain, developer Cellar Door Games has <a href="https://twitter.com/CellarDoorGames/status/1245811726546808834?s=20">confirmed</a> that, yes, it really is working on a sequel to its superb Castlevania-esque rogue-like exploratory platformer Rogue Legacy.</p><p>The original Rogue Legacy, if you're unfamiliar, launched all the way back in 2013, and won immediate acclaim for its solid, procedurally generated action-platforming, bolstered by a compelling upgrade loop, and a nifty system that saw each subsequent play-through undertaken by one of your previous, now-dead hero's heirs.</p><p>Wonderfully, each new descendant was imbued with a distinctive mix of classes, abilities, and traits, combining to make each new play-through feel surprisingly, refreshingly different; new heroes might become tiny in stature or super strong, while others might be dyslexic (jumbling up all in-game text), colour blind (turning the world black and white), and a <a href="https://rogue-legacy.fandom.com/wiki/Category:Traits">whole lot more</a>.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-acclaimed-rogue-like-platformer-rogue-legacy-is-getting-a-sequel">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-acclaimed-rogue-like-platformer-rogue-legacy-is-getting-a-sequel</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089164</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 23:16:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>80 Days dev reveals King-Arthur-inspired &quot;strategic narrative&quot; adventure Pendragon</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-21-12/80-days-dev-reveals-king-arthure-inspired-strategic-narrative-game-pendragon-1585858353198.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089152.jpg" alt=""/><p>Inkle Studios, the developer behind the wonderful 80 Days and Heaven's Vault, has, after some <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-01-31-heavens-vault-developer-teases-a-journey-into-arthurian-legend-for-its-next-game">early teasing back in February</a>, finally unveiled its next project. It's called Pendragon, and is described as a "strategic narrative" adventure inspired by Arthurian legend.</p><p>Pendragon unfolds in the year AD 673, with Camelot on the verge of destruction. The fellowship of the Round Table is in disarray, thanks to Sir Modred's deceit, and it's up to you to assemble a ragtag band of knights, heroes, and peasants, traverse the treacherous Britain of the Dark Ages and, hopefully, lend your assistance to King Arthur on the other side.</p><p>"Will Sir Lancelot be reunited with Queen Guinevere? Will she spurn him, or embrace him?," teases Inkle, "Will Sir Kay ever forgive Sir Gawaine for siding with Sir Mordred? Can Morgana le Fay be trusted? Where is Merlyn? Who lies buried in Mordred's graveyard? Who is the archer in the woods? What has become of Excalibur?".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-80-days-dev-reveals-king-arthur-inspired-strategic-narrative-game-pendragon">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-80-days-dev-reveals-king-arthur-inspired-strategic-narrative-game-pendragon</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089152</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 21:09:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Last of Us Part 2, Iron Man VR delayed &quot;until further notice&quot;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-19-22/-1585851739207.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089139.jpg" alt=""/><p>Sony says the release of The Last of Us Part 2 and Marvel's Iron Man VR will be delayed "until further notice" as a result of the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</p><p>The news comes via a <a href="https://twitter.com/PlayStation/status/1245773000592384001?s=20">post to the official PlayStation Twitter feed</a>, which explains the company has made the "difficult decision" to delay both PlayStation 4 titles as, "Logistically, the global crisis is preventing us from providing the launch experience our players deserve".</p><p>While Sony's rather cryptic use of the phrase "launch experience" doesn't exactly shed light on the specifics behind its decision to indefinitely delay The Last of Us Part 2 and Iron Man VR, Naughty Dog elaborated further in its own <a href="https://twitter.com/Naughty_Dog/status/1245773177944281089?s=20">follow-up statement</a>, reassuring fans that development on The Last of Us Part 2 is "nearly done" and that the studio is currently "in the midst of fixing our final bugs".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-the-last-of-us-part-2-iron-man-vr-delayed-until-further-notice">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-the-last-of-us-part-2-iron-man-vr-delayed-until-further-notice</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089139</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 19:20:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Apex Legends gets permanent duos and a Bloodhound event</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-17-06/apex-legends-gets-permanent-duos-and-bloodhound-event-1585843580967.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089107.jpg" alt=""/><p>Good things may come in threes, but now they'll come in twos, too - as Apex Legends is adding a permanent duos mode. Along with permanent rotation between maps and a new Bloodhound-themed town takeover. There's a lot happening. </p><p>From 7th to 21st April, players will be able to take part in an event called The Old Ways, focused on hunter legend Bloodhound. As a town takeover event similar to Octane's, Bloodhound is getting a themed takeover on World's Edge - and players will need to "battle ferocious prowlers for their chance at high-tier loot". I believe that's the lion-snake creature from Titanfall, by the way, not the guns. Players can scoop up goodies as a reward for venturing into this area, but I imagine it will also become a bit of a hot drop. Bringing a Bloodhound with your squad will help, apparently. </p><p>As part of the event, there will be an Old Ways prize track, in which players can earn up to 1000 points per challenge set, with challenges refreshing on a daily basis. You can also just directly purchase event-exclusive legendary skins from the shop. There's also a nice digital short about Bloodhound's "path from small village to Apex Arena", should you want to deepen your understanding of Apex lore.  </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-apex-legends-gets-permanent-duos-and-bloodhound-event">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-apex-legends-gets-permanent-duos-and-bloodhound-event</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089107</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Annapurna Interactive's apocalyptic coming-of-age visual novel If Found is out in May</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-18-52/annapurnas-if-found-is-an-interactive-novel-about-going-home-coming-out-and-erasing-everything-1585849937225.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089119.jpg" alt=""/><p>Annapurna Interactive, the publisher behind the critically acclaimed likes of What Remains of Edith Finch and Outer Wilds, has announced that If Found, its visual novel about "going home, coming out and erasing everything", will launch on Steam, Mac, and iOS on 19th May.</p><p>If Found is the work of Irish developer Dreamfeel, and its story begin (or perhaps more accurately, ends) on 31st December 1993, on the night that a black hole threatens to destroy the world. Here, in the remains of a dilapidated mansion on Achill Island, County Mayo, a young woman named Kasio destroys her diary - erasing memories of her return home to Ireland, "her conflict with her family, the friends she makes, and the challenges she goes through".</p><p>As you'd expect given its "visual novel" label, If Found is a predominantly text-driven narrative adventure, albeit one that's ably supported by some wonderfully striking, lightly animated visuals - blending a range of elements, from pencil sketches and ink to water colour - as Kasio revisits, and relinquishes, her past in the face of her rapidly diminishing future.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-annapurna-interactives-apocalyptic-coming-of-age-visual-novel-if-found-is-out-in-may">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-annapurna-interactives-apocalyptic-coming-of-age-visual-novel-if-found-is-out-in-may</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089119</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 17:50:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>If you own Fallout 76 on Bethesda.net, you can get a Steam copy free</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-16-50/if-you-own-fallout-76-on-bethesda-net-you-can-get-a-steam-copy-free-1585842607754.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089103.jpg" alt=""/><p>Bethesda has made the upcoming Steam version of Fallout 76 free to those who own the game on Bethesda's launcher.</p><p>If you own Fallout 76 on Bethesda.net and you link your Steam account by 13th April, you get a Steam copy free.</p><p>The promotion comes ahead of the launch of Fallout 76's long-awaited and free Wastelanders expansion, which adds NPCs and story content to the MMO. Wastelanders and Fallout 76 launch on Steam on 14th April.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-if-you-own-fallout-76-on-bethesda-net-you-can-get-a-steam-copy-free">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-if-you-own-fallout-76-on-bethesda-net-you-can-get-a-steam-copy-free</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089103</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 16:54:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Borderlands 3 devs say they won't get promised bonuses</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-16-04/borderlands-3-devs-say-their-promised-bonuses-have-been-slashed-1585839888028.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089089.jpg" alt=""/><p>Given it's one of gaming's biggest franchises, the news Borderlands 3 was a major success came as little surprise. Within its first five days, it sold over five million copies - <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-09-23-borderlands-3-is-the-fastest-selling-game-in-2ks-history_7">making it 2K's fastest-selling game of all time</a>. </p><p>Something that probably did come as a surprise to Borderlands 3's developers, however, is that their hefty bonuses designed to make up for lower initial pay were no longer happening. </p><p>That's according to a report by <a href="https://kotaku.com/sources-despite-huge-sales-borderlands-3-developers-a-1842617645">Kotaku</a>, whose sources say Gearbox employees will no longer receive the royalty bonuses promised throughout development. The news was apparently broken yesterday by CEO Randy Pitchford, who said developers would now receive much smaller bonus checks than the ones expected (which in some cases were supposed to go into the tens or hundreds of thousands). The reason given was that the game had been more expensive than anticipated, combined with significant company growth and off-base sales projections. The increased expense was likely caused by a technology swap between Unreal Engine 3 and Unreal Engine 4 mid-way through development, along with a 2K deal which meant Gearbox needed to first recoup both Borderlands 3's $95m (£76.6m) budget and the DLC budget (for a combined total of nearly $145m or £112m) before the studio could receive royalties. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-borderlands-3-devs-say-their-promised-bonuses-have-been-slashed">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-borderlands-3-devs-say-their-promised-bonuses-have-been-slashed</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089089</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 16:34:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Boundary looks like the zero-gravity bits from Call of Duty: Infinite Warfare</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-15-41/-1585838480942.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089084.jpg" alt=""/><p>Remember the zero-gravity sections from the unfairly maligned Call of Duty: Infinite Warfare? Boundary is a new upcoming first-person shooter that takes those bits and runs with them.</p><p>Boundary, due out on PlayStation 4 and PC at some point in 2020, is about zero-gravity shootouts with high-tech weaponry in outer space. The soldiers in the game are armed astronauts called Astroperators, or AOs. You have full freedom of movement and, as you'd expect from a game set in space, you are unrestricted from gravity. As a result, you can use floating debris as cover and propel forward with the help of your grapple hook.</p><p>In the trailer below, we see the solar farm map, with giant reflectors as well as a glimpse at the tactical shield and re-forged AK rifle. Expect multiple Astroperators classes, 5v5, 3v3 and 2v2 competitive multiplayer.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-ps4-and-pc-fps-boundary-looks-like-the-zero-gravity-bits-from-call-of-duty-infinite-warfare">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-ps4-and-pc-fps-boundary-looks-like-the-zero-gravity-bits-from-call-of-duty-infinite-warfare</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089084</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 15:38:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Sea of Thieves sets sail for Steam</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-15-18/-1585837092666.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089077.jpg" alt=""/><p>Sea of Thieves will get a Steam release, which will include full crossplay with the game's existing Windows 10 and Xbox One versions. </p><p>You can <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1172620/Sea_of_Thieves/" target="_blank">wishlist</a> it today, Microsoft said, with a launch date to be announced "soon". </p><p>The news comes as Rare's buccaneering pirate simulate passes a milestone of 10 million unique players, including those who've jumped aboard via Xbox Game Pass. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-sea-of-thieves-sets-sail-for-steam">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-sea-of-thieves-sets-sail-for-steam</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089077</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 15:23:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft eyes impact of Xbox Series X software developed from home</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-14-51/-1585835474551.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089062.jpg" alt=""/><p>Microsoft remains confident its Xbox Series X console will be ready for launch at the end of this year, but is keeping a close eye on its software side - its games and system services - many of which are now being developed remotely. </p><p>Supply chains for the hardware itself are starting to pick up as factories in China re-open, but as the coronavirus pandemic spreads, Microsoft's teams working on the console's firmware and launch game line-up are having to get used to working from home.</p><p>In a wide-ranging interview with <a href="https://uk.ign.com/articles/interview-head-of-xbox-phil-spencer-talking-xbox-series-x-a-unlocked-437">IGN</a>, Xbox boss Phil Spencer (speaking from his own home office) said these teams are being "stretched" as they work remotely - that their safety came first, and that he wouldn't hold back the console if launch line-up star Halo: Infinite slipped.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-microsoft-eyes-impact-of-xbox-series-x-software-being-developed-from-home">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-microsoft-eyes-impact-of-xbox-series-x-software-being-developed-from-home</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089062</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 14:59:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Nintendo Switch eShop Spring Sale drops hundreds of games by up to 80%</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-14-21/the_witcher_3_wild_hunt_gog_spring_sale.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089022.jpg" alt=""/><p>After teasing us with a tweet earlier this week, the Spring Sale has launched on the Nintendo Switch eShop with discounts on over 300 games including Diablo 3 Eternal Collection, The Witcher 3 and Octopath Traveller.</p><p>There are some great offers available but, as we've come to expect from Nintendo sales, you won't find any massive reductions on the most-wanted first-party games - at least right now.</p><p>Nope, the highlights at the moment are a mix of popular third-party releases and some of the console's most popular indies. Of course, with over 300 games in the sale, it's hard to list everything right here. I've picked out a few of the more interesting ones here (and highlighted some particuarly good deals in bold) but you should definitely have a browse through the full <a href="https://www.nintendo.co.uk/Nintendo-eShop/Nintendo-eShop-Sale/Nintendo-eShop-Sale-1460557.html" target="_blank">Nintendo eShop Spring Sale</a> page to see what else is hiding away.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-nintendo-switch-eshop-spring-sale">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-nintendo-switch-eshop-spring-sale</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089022</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 14:24:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Super cool Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 Campaign Remastered Easter egg fixes nine-year-old No Russian continuity error</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-14-07/cool-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-campaign-remastered-easter-egg-fixes-nine-year-old-no-russian-continuity-error-1585832856253.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089043.jpg" alt=""/><p>The Call of Duty series is known for its Easter eggs - but this is perhaps the best one yet.</p><p><strong>THERE MAY BE SPOILERS AHEAD.</strong></p><p>This week, Activision released Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 Campaign Remastered (<a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remaster-launches-tomorrow">as a month-long PlayStation 4 timed-exclusive, criminally</a>), and its developers have taken the opportunity to slip in a super cool Easter egg that fixes a nine-year-old continuity error.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-cool-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-campaign-remastered-easter-egg-fixes-nine-year-old-no-russian-continuity-error">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-cool-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-campaign-remastered-easter-egg-fixes-nine-year-old-no-russian-continuity-error</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089043</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 14:13:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Animal Crossing's Zipper T Bunny doesn't deserve your hate</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-13-44/who-is-animal-crossings-zipper-t-bunny-an-investigation-1585831468341.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089037.jpg" alt=""/><p>Yesterday an uninvited guest visited my Animal Crossing: New Horizons island - and I, like many others, found him a little creepy. </p><p>This is Zipper T. Bunny, the rabbit who appears before the <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/animal-crossing-bunny-day-dates-easter-event-items-new-horizons-7018">annual Bunny Day</a> event to task you with collecting limitless amounts of eggs for a reward. Or is he? As the name may suggest, Zipper has a zip on his back, and despite his protestations of being a real rabbit something is definitely amiss. </p><p>"I know what you're thinking," Zipper tells you under his breath, after reciting some horrible lines in rhyme. "No. This is NOT a costume. And don't you go snoopin', got it?" </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-who-is-animal-crossings-zipper-t-bunny-an-investigation">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-who-is-animal-crossings-zipper-t-bunny-an-investigation</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089037</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 14:11:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>PlayStation 5 uncovered: the Mark Cerny tech deep dive</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-19-49/digitalfoundry-2020-playstation-5-the-mark-cerny-tech-deep-dive-1585507750705.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088245.jpg" alt=""/><p>On March 18th, Sony finally broke cover with in-depth information on the technical make-up of PlayStation 5. Expanding significantly on previously discussed topics and revealing lots of new information on the system's core specifications, lead system architect Mark Cerny delivered a developer-centric presentation that laid out the core foundations of PlayStation 5: power, bandwidth, speed, and immersion. A couple of days prior to the talk going live, Digital Foundry spoke in depth with Cerny on the topics covered. Some of that discussion informed our <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-playstation-5-specs-and-tech-that-deliver-sonys-next-gen-vision" target="_blank">initial coverage</a>, but we have more information. A lot more.</p><p>But to be clear here, everything in this piece centres on the topics in Cerny's discussion. There's much to assimilate here, but what you won't get are any further revelations about PlayStation 5 strategy - and it's not for want of asking. In our prior meeting back in 2016, Cerny talked in depth about how Sony was wedded to the concept of the console generation and the hardware revealed certainly attests to that. So is cross-gen development a thing for first-party developers? While stressing again that he's all in on the concept of console generations (as opposed to PC-style, more gradual innovation) he wasn't going to talk software strategy, and to be fair, that's not really his area. </p><p>Cerny also delivered PlayStation 4 - which he defined as 'super-charged PC architecture' way back in 2013. It was an approach that helped deliver a developer-friendly multi-platform golden age... but is PlayStation 5 a return to the more 'exotic' philosophy we saw in prior generation console design? Cerny shared little, except to say that PS5 design is easy for PlayStation 4 developers to get to grips with, but digging deeper into the new system's capabilities, there are many aspects of the PS5 design that PCs will be hard-pressed to match. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-playstation-5-the-mark-cerny-tech-deep-dive">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-playstation-5-the-mark-cerny-tech-deep-dive</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088245</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>In Other Waters review - an ocean sanctuary for the meditative explorer</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-15-33/in-other-waters-review-1585665232831.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088619.jpg" alt=""/><p>It begins with one of the loveliest interfaces I've ever handled, a fluorescent origami puzzle of panels, dials and buttons, at once tactile and ethereal, vintage and high-tech, like a holographic astrolabe. At its centre, a circle of ocean rendered in the style of an old-time sea chart, its delicately nested contours travelling beyond the dashboard into a turquoise haze.</p><p>A tap of space bar sends out a wailing sonar wave, populating that circle of water with triangular waypoints and coloured dots, darting through or forming undulating patterns - creatures, going about their lives without much heed for the fumbling, dive-suited human in their midst. Tap a waypoint to scan it, a brief but evocative description filling a fold-out panel to the right. Push one of the larger buttons to set that waypoint as a destination, a sextant arm locking across the view with a gratifying click. Hit another button to engage the suit's thrusters, then hit space on arrival to scan your surroundings anew. </p><p>This is the heartbeat of In Other Waters, a unique and mesmerising exploration game from Jump Over The Age, set on an alien planet. It's a tempo that carries you from sunlit shallows to waters clogged with poisonous microbes, from pillars decked with pollen to abyssal reaches that harbour dreadful secrets. There is little to break the rhythm - no in-game antagonist to defeat, and only a small handful of tools such as laser cutters that open up initially inaccessible regions. Even the occasional terrain hazards, which range from stinging veils to pools of corrosive brine, are more like encouragements to keep moving than threats.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-in-other-waters-review">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-in-other-waters-review</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088619</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:23:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>No, Scalebound isn't back in production</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-12-08/-1585825728812.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089016.jpg" alt=""/><p>
Scalebound, the Xbox One console exclusive once in development at Platinum Games, was <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2017-01-09-sources-microsoft-and-platinum-part-ways-on-scalebound-development-ceased">cancelled three years ago</a> - but in the past year, rumours have persisted of a revival.</p><p>One wild piece of speculation floating round the internet of late suggested it could even see a new lease of life for Nintendo Switch. And while there was never any evidence of this, Microsoft has at last set the record straight. </p><p>Speaking to <a href="https://uk.ign.com/articles/interview-head-of-xbox-phil-spencer-talking-xbox-series-x-a-unlocked-437">IGN</a>, Xbox boss Phil Spencer has said Microsoft was "not working on it" and that it was "something we've all moved past", while admitting regrets over how the game's development unfolded.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-no-scalebound-isnt-back-in-production">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-no-scalebound-isnt-back-in-production</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089016</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 12:10:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Judge rules Call of Duty can depict Humvees without a licence</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-11-59/-1585825140676.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2089010.jpg" alt=""/><p>A judge has ruled Call of Duty can depict Humvees without a licence.</p><p>In 2017, AM General LLC, the company behind the Humvee, <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2017-11-09-humvee-suing-activision-over-call-of-duty">sued Activision over the appearance of the famous military vehicle in Call of Duty</a>.</p><p>The Humvee has appeared in most of the Modern Warfare games. In one mission in the recently-remastered Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2, you man a Humvee gunner during a drive through an Afghanistan town.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-judge-rules-call-of-duty-can-depict-humvees-without-a-licence">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-judge-rules-call-of-duty-can-depict-humvees-without-a-licence</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2089010</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 11:51:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Sony sets up $100m COVID-19 relief fund</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-09-58/sony-sets-up-USD100m-covid-19-global-relief-fund-1585817882178.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088966.jpg" alt=""/><p>Sony has set up a $100m COVID-19 relief fund.</p><p>The fund is designed to support those around the world affected by the coronavirus.</p><p>According to the World Health Organisation, the number of infections globally will reach a million within days, and there is growing concern in several countries about supplies of protection equipment for medical workers.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-sony-sets-up-usd100m-covid-19-global-relief-fund">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-sony-sets-up-usd100m-covid-19-global-relief-fund</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088966</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 09:55:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Hands-on with the dual-screen, ultra-premium Asus ROG Zephyrus Duo 15</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-02-21/hands-on-with-the-dual-screen-ultra-premium-rog-zephyrus-duo-15-1585790514213.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088857.jpg" alt=""/><p>The first laptops with <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-intel-announces-10th-gen-comet-lake-h-laptop-processors-with-up-to-5-3ghz-turbo">Intel Comet Lake H processors</a> and Nvidia RTX Super graphics cards are on the way soon, and we've already gone hands on with a few of them thanks to a recent Asus press event. The star of the show there was the ROG Zephyrus Duo 15, a hyper-modern machine that is the best argument for dual-screen laptops we've seen to date.</p><p>Like the Asus Zenbook Pro Duo, a dual-screen laptop released last year, the laptop's 14-inch secondary display sits beneath the main 15-inch screen, offering about the same width and nearly half the height with a resolution of 3840x1100. <i>Unlike</i> that machine though, the secondary screen automatically angles upwards as the lid of the laptop is opened, ensuring that you're not looking at the screen off-axis and allowing a 28.5mm air intake to be exposed. </p><p>The mechanism here is robust too; the touch screen didn't shift a millimetre under even the harshest of taps and worked silently even on the pre-production machine we had access to. The transformation is fascinating to watch, the sort of thing you'll want to do just for the joy of it, and that's a rarity on laptops these days.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-hands-on-with-the-dual-screen-ultra-premium-rog-zephyrus-duo-15">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-hands-on-with-the-dual-screen-ultra-premium-rog-zephyrus-duo-15</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088857</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:01:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Intel announces 10th-gen Comet Lake H laptop CPUs with up to 5.3GHz turbo</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-02-01-37/intel-announces-10th-gen-comet-lake-h-laptop-processors-with-up-to-5-3ghz-turbo-1585787856917.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088924.jpg" alt=""/><p>Intel unveiled its 10th-generation Comet Lake H-series mobile processors today, unlocking a new tier of high performance parts for gaming and creation-focused laptops. These are the highest-clocked CPUs we've ever seen from Intel, with the flagship eight-core, sixteen-thread Core i9-10980HK processor turboing all the way up to 5.3GHz - a 300MHz jump over the previous generation equivalent. </p><p>This frequency focus is also reflected in the rest of the new processor family too, with all three Core i7 SKUs in Comet Lake H capable of boosting to 5GHz or higher. Even the most affordable chips see a sizeable gen-on-gen clockspeed increase, with the two Core i5 models in the family hitting the same frequencies as last generation's Core i7 models. It's an interesting approach to mobile processor design, where high frequencies are normally eschewed for reasons of efficiency, but it could result in some uniquely performant gaming laptops.</p><p>Before we take a closer look at what distinguishes these 10th-generation processors from their predecessors - and there are some new features to discuss - let's take a look at the full lineup:</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-intel-announces-10th-gen-comet-lake-h-laptop-processors-with-up-to-5-3ghz-turbo">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-intel-announces-10th-gen-comet-lake-h-laptop-processors-with-up-to-5-3ghz-turbo</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088924</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:01:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 Campaign Remastered brings the series' confounding pinnacle into brilliant focus</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-17-07/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered-brings-the-series-confounding-pinnacle-into-brilliant-focus-1585757275014.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088868.jpg" alt=""/><p>There are two games that live side-by-side in Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2. One is an all-time action classic, thrilling and tense and more than a little ridiculous in its recounting of the heroics of war; the other, meanwhile, is a fierce and surprisingly cutting anti-war critique. The result, certainly when I first played it back in 2009, is oil and water. They don't mix, at least on the surface, and for many that means neither half of the game really lands. The parable is obscured by the action, the action is obscured by the parable, and you're left with a nagging sense that this is supposed to mean <em>something</em>, between the lines of the Hoorahs and the Tango Downs, but it's unclear exactly what.</p><p>I have struggled to pin down why I love it, some fond nostalgia-tinged memories of multiplayer aside. I've always known Modern Warfare 2 to be a mess - a beautiful mess, but still a mess - that's unquestionably fun and smarter than it looks, but still lacking the requisite nuance to land its point. It took the added sheen of quite stunning photorealism, brought to it by Beenox's surprise remaster - and, more likely, just another replay of the story anyway - to really figure it out. The impact, now, of emerging midway through the game to a smashed Washington Monument and a White House ablaze, or of breaking free from the Gulag, or creeping through waves of snow, is honestly extraordinary. But on top of that the game's narrative tricks seem to come into sharper focus, too. The story's major beats just hitting a little harder, the brilliance shining a little brighter.</p><p>It's worth retreading (and <strong>spoilers</strong> for an 11-year-old game here, as a heads up). Modern Warfare 2 is a game about American - and specifically American - interventionism, of which it is blisteringly critical. "We are the most powerful military force in the history of man", American General Shepherd rumbles in the first line of the game post-tutorial. "Every fight is our fight." Shepherd, of course, goes on to reveal himself as the architect of a false flag operation - clunkily delivered via <em>that</em> mission - that brings about a Russian invasion of the United States and, in Shepherd's later words, "no shortage of recruits" to the US military for years to come. As <a href="https://kotaku.com/modern-warfare-2-deserves-more-credit-1707059737" target="_blank">others have put it before me</a>, Shepherd is really a stand-in here for something bigger than his role in the game's own, somewhat tangled plot: namely for the notion of perpetual war itself, for the philosophy of an interventionist global force, a cultural hunger for intercontinental violence.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered-brings-the-series-confounding-pinnacle-into-brilliant-focus">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-02-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered-brings-the-series-confounding-pinnacle-into-brilliant-focus</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088868</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Pong Quest is a &quot;hilarious&quot; dungeon-crawling spin on the arcade classic</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-23-32/pong-quest-is-a-hilarious-dungeon-crawling-spin-on-the-arcade-classic-1585780364530.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088923.jpg" alt=""/><p>Ever spent an afternoon pondering the inherent deficiencies of arcade classic Pong? Ever said to yourself in a flash of inspiration, "What this seminal bat battler really needs is jokes! And dungeons! And a paddle with a moustache!"? If so, congratulations! You are Atari and have just invented Pong Quest, the newly announced "hilarious" dungeon crawling spin on the legendary arcade game, coming to pretty much everything this spring.</p><p>Pong Quest - which, as far as I can tell, is the first official new outing for the series since 2012's Pong World - casts players as a "cheerful and adorable" Pong paddle, as it embarks on a vaguely RPG-like adventure to save the world from imminent destruction.</p><p>What that amounts to in gameplay terms is a bit of exploratory dungeon roaming - each new area is said to be loosely themed around classic Atari properties, including Asteroids and Centipede - with enemy encounters being resolved through spiced-up Pong battles, featuring over 50 Pong ball varieties adding "new depths and strategy".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-pong-quest-is-a-hilarious-dungeon-crawling-spin-on-the-arcade-classic">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-pong-quest-is-a-hilarious-dungeon-crawling-spin-on-the-arcade-classic</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088923</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 23:09:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Someone's recreated Zelda: A Link to the Past's map in Animal Crossing: New Horizons</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-21-06/someones-created-zelda-a-link-to-the-pasts-overworld-in-animal-crossing-new-horizons-1585771566644.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088889.jpg" alt=""/><p>While some of us have spent the start of Bunny Day frantically launching projectiles into the air as if in the midst of some apocalyptic invasion (although actually just because we really want those flying eggs), other Animal Crossing: New Horizons players have been putting their indoor time to far more productive use - with one such person turning their entire island into a surprisingly convincing recreation of Zelda: A Link to the Past's iconic overworld map.</p><p>The brains behind this ambitious endeavour goes by the name of VaynMaanen on Reddit, and <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AnimalCrossing/comments/fsjyv8/after_4_grueling_days_of_terraforming_ive_modeled/">unveiled the fruits of their terraforming toils</a>, which apparently took four days to complete, in a series of screenshots to the Animal Crossing subreddit earlier today. </p><p>As the comparison image below shows, the similarities are striking, even accepting the creative compromises required for those Zelda elements tricky to accurately recreate in-game. All waterways and elevated terrain are present and correct, including the looming (or as looming as New Horizon's height restrictions allow, at least) Death Mountain, and there's even a recreation of Kakariko Village to the west, formed from a huddle of islander homes.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-someones-recreated-zelda-a-link-to-the-pasts-map-in-animal-crossing-new-horizons">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-someones-recreated-zelda-a-link-to-the-pasts-map-in-animal-crossing-new-horizons</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088889</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 20:09:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Uncharted 4, Dirt Rally 2.0 are April's PlayStation Plus games</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-17-52/uncharted-4-dirt-rally-2-0-are-aprils-playstation-plus-games-1585759964734.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088878.jpg" alt=""/><p>Another month, another fresh selection of titles waiting in the wings for PlayStation Plus subscribers to download, and April is a <a href="https://blog.eu.playstation.com/2020/04/01/uncharted-4-a-thiefs-end-and-dirt-rally-2-0-are-your-playstation-plus-games-for-april/">particularly strong showing</a> for the service, ushering in Uncharted 4: A Thief's End and Dirt Rally 2.0.</p><p>Starting next Tuesday, 7th April, eligible humans can plot a course for adventure, courtesy of Nathan Drake's latest (and last) treasure hunting escapade, which initially released on PS4 back in 2016. It's a good 'un too, packing in the series usual set-piece heavy bouts of exploratory action, albeit with the 'spectacular' dial cranked right up to the maximum.</p><p>"As accomplished as Uncharted 4: A Thief's End is - as heroically as it bests its predecessors, as gracefully as it sidesteps their pitfalls - it's not possible for it to have the seismic impact and far-reaching influence that Uncharted 2 did," said Oli Welsh in his <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2016-05-05-uncharted-4-review">Recommended review</a>, "Nor does it redefine the storytelling scope of the blockbuster action game like The Last of Us."</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-uncharted-4-dirt-rally-2-0-are-aprils-playstation-plus-games">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-uncharted-4-dirt-rally-2-0-are-aprils-playstation-plus-games</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088878</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:44:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Someone tried to rob me in Animal Crossing</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-16-52/-1585756352289.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088861.jpg" alt=""/><p>It was a week after I'd <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-25-i-set-up-an-animal-crossing-swap-shop-and-now-were-helping-defeat-tom-nook">established my swap shop in Animal Crossing: New Horizons</a>, and things had been going surprisingly well. After testing it with friends I'd opened my island up to the wider community via dodo code, and most people were behaving. Guests were swapping out unwanted items and finding new trinkets to take home, with many showing stunning generosity and sending kind messages. There were a couple who stretched the rules by leaving flowers or a single iron nugget, but I was willing to forgive them (particularly given someone had donated 300k bells to cover costs). Demand had grown so great, in fact, that I'd even set up a <a href="https://twitter.com/ACswapshop">swap shop Twitter account</a> just to manage all the requests to visit. </p><p>And then, as always, someone tried to ruin it all.</p><p>I was minding my own business managing the shop when, glancing down from my Nook phone, I noticed a mysterious absence of fruit in one section of the shop. Maybe someone was swapping out a lot of fruit at once? Odd. Putting my phone away, I saw that half the items in the swap shop had vanished - and the culprit was mid-way through hoovering up the remaining goods. They clearly had no intention of swapping anything, and were well on their way to simply clearing out the stock.  </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-someone-tried-to-rob-me-in-animal-crossing">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-someone-tried-to-rob-me-in-animal-crossing</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088861</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:07:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bethesda will skip holding digital event in June</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-16-48/-1585756105216.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088864.jpg" alt=""/><p>The usual announcements at this year's <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-11-it-looks-like-e3-is-cancelled">now-cancelled E3</a> will be replaced by various publisher digital events - but don't expect a showcase from Bethesda. </p><p>The Fallout and Elder Scrolls publisher has today announced it will not host a June livestream due to the "many challenges" the company now faces amid the ongoing coronavirus crisis. </p><p>Fans keen to hear more on the studio's upcoming projects - especially those slated to hit the next generation of consoles - will now need to wait a little longer. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-bethesda-will-skip-holding-digital-event-in-june">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-bethesda-will-skip-holding-digital-event-in-june</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088864</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 16:50:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rayman Legends is currently free on PC until the end of the week</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-16-57/rayman-legends-is-currently-free-for-a-few-days-on-pc-1585756637309.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088866.jpg" alt=""/><p>Sublime platformer Rayman Legends is currently available to download for free and keep forever on PC, courtesy of the Ubisoft Store, but you'll need to move swiftly, as the offer expires at the end of the week.</p><p>And if you're in the market for some free entertainment to break up the monotony of roaming your halls forlornly, occasionally peering out the windows in sweet reminisce, you could do considerably worse than Rayman Legends, as it's an absolute treat.</p><p>Released in 2013, it's the follow-up to the only marginally less delightful Rayman Origins, and like that game, takes the Rayman series' classic 2D platforming and re-invigorates it with some consistently wonderful presentation and relentlessly inventive level design.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-rayman-legends-is-currently-free-on-pc-until-the-end-of-the-week">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-rayman-legends-is-currently-free-on-pc-until-the-end-of-the-week</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088866</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 16:49:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Humble launches the Conquer Covid-19 Bundle to support organisations fighting coronavirus</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-16-08/conquercovid_bundle_meta.png/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088837.jpg" alt=""/><p>Humble's has launched the Conquer Covid-19 Bundle featuring over $1000 of games and ebooks with all proceeds going to support the efforts of various organisations tackling the global pandemic.</p><p>It's a substantial haul, that includes loads of indie hits, classic favourites, insightful learning books and terrific graphic novels. Listing everything here would likely risk breaking your scroll wheel, so I've picked out a few standouts below to give you an idea of what's included. You can check out everything for yourself on the <a href="https://www.humblebundle.com/conquer-covid19-bundle" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Humble Conquer Covid-19 Bundle</a> page.</p><p>In terms of games, highlights easily include ingenious strategy gem Into the Breach, unconventional RPG Undertale, enthralling adventure game Hollow Knight and pensive puzzler The Witness. There's good representation from Darksiders, Jackbox and many classics from Double Fine, too.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-humble-launches-the-conquer-covid-19-bundle-to-support-organisations-fighting-coronavirus">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-humble-launches-the-conquer-covid-19-bundle-to-support-organisations-fighting-coronavirus</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088837</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 16:13:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Flipnote Studio April Fool's ends in creator being harassed</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-14-55/-1585749312481.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088823.jpg" alt=""/><p>Numerous Nintendo fans (and fan sites) this week fell foul of a fake Flipnote Studio revival - and now the person behind the intended April Fool's joke is receiving a torrent of abuse.</p><p>It all began at the weekend, when a detailed set of images popped up online purporting to be of a Switch remake for the DS and 3DS doodler. The screenshots were said to have been posted by a Japanese user who gained access to a beta version, and included illustrations of obscure Nintendo characters from forgotten games such as Giftpia and Chibi-Robo. Some fans took these to be teases for new games in those series, too.</p><p>Flipnote Studio was a popular animation app made by Nintendo originally for the DSi, with a sequel for 3DS. It lets artists showcase simple drawings and animation, and grew to have a cult following.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-flipnote-studio-joke-which-began-as-april-fools-ends-in-creator-being-harassed">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-flipnote-studio-joke-which-began-as-april-fools-ends-in-creator-being-harassed</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088823</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:47:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Save up to £60 on PC hardware, gaming laptops and 4K TVs at Ebay today</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-13-43/get-15-percent-off-at-ebay-outlets-1585745009215.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088789.jpg" alt=""/><p>Ebay's semi-regular <a href="https://www.ebay.co.uk/e/coupon-offers/april01-generic">15 per cent off deal</a> has returned once again, offering an excellent chance to pick up a wide range of new and used tech from top retailers at some of the best prices you're likely to see all year. Here's what you need to know - plus Digital Foundry's sale highlights. </p><p><strong>Rules</strong>: This time around, the minimum spend is £20 and the maximum discount is £60, so the best deals are around the £400 mark. Two redemptions of the code are allowed per account, with the sale starting today and running until April 4th at 11:59PM. (<a href="https://pages.ebay.co.uk/coupons/2019/pl387/index.html/">Full terms are here</a>.) </p><p><strong>Code</strong>: To get the discount, use code <strong>POP15</strong> at the checkout on items from one of the <a href="https://pages.ebay.co.uk/coupons/2019/pl387/index.html/">156 Ebay outlets</a> taking part in the promotion. Items that offer the discount will include a small notice below the price, which looks like this on desktop web browsers:</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-get-15-percent-off-at-ebay-4k-tvs-macbooks-pc-hardware">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-04-01-get-15-percent-off-at-ebay-4k-tvs-macbooks-pc-hardware</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088789</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:24:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Warhammer 40,000 aerial combat tabletop Aeronautica Imperialis has a turn-based strategy game</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-15-07/warhammer-40-000-aerial-combat-tabletop-aeronautica-imperialis-has-a-strategy-video-game-1585750029243.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088825.jpg" alt=""/><p>The Warhammer 40,000 video games keep on coming! This one is based on the aerial combat tabletop Aeronautica Imperialis.</p><p>Unlike <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-02-21-new-warhammer-40k-aerial-combat-game-gives-orks-a-starring-role">Dakka Squadron</a>, an action-focused Warhammer 40,000 aerial combat game that gives Orks a starring role, Aeronautica Imperialis: Flight Command is a turn-based strategy game. You play as a Flight Commander in the Imperial Navy or a Skwadron Kommanda of the Ork Air Waaagh!, commanding Thunderbolts, Marauder Bombers, Fightas and Bommas in dog fights.</p><p>Expect fully-licensed models from Games Workshop, seven story-driven scenarios playable single-player or head-to-head online, and a training system.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-warhammer-40-000-aerial-combat-tabletop-aeronautica-imperialis-has-a-strategy-video-game">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-warhammer-40-000-aerial-combat-tabletop-aeronautica-imperialis-has-a-strategy-video-game</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088825</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:09:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Resident Evil 3 demo analysis: the game's brilliant but something's up with Xbox One X</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-23-12-49/-1584967792996.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2087194.jpg" alt=""/><p><strong>UPDATE 1/4/20 2pm:</strong> Digital Foundry has completed its testing of the release version of the Resident Evil 3 remake and found that the playable demo currently available to all users is indeed a good indication of performance in the retail game, meaning that of all the console versions available, PlayStation 4 Pro offers the most consistent experience and is our recommended pick. Meanwhile, as with the demo, Xbox One X trades too much in performance terms in exchange for its 2160p rendering. Traversing the console power ladder, frame-rates on the base consoles continue to be variable, with Xbox One S running at a disadvantage compared to PlayStation 4.</p><p>We asked Capcom for comment about the Xbox One X showing and got this statement: "Capcom is definitely aware of the fan feedback with regards to Xbox performance, so they may look into providing a solution sometime after launch." From our perspective, we would hope to see the option to choose between higher frame-rates at 1620p (as per the X's pixel count in Resident Evil 2 Remake) or an image quality mode for the current 2160p set-up.</p><p>In truth though, while the focus has been on Xbox One X's issues, we also think that the option to lock console performance to 30fps would be a welcome addition to a prospective patch - and while this would be ideal for Xbox One X's 2160p output, it would benefit the standard vanilla consoles especially. As you'll see in the video report below, the inconsistency in frame-rate on the standard machines isn't exactly ideal. We'll report back if any update to the Resident Evil 3 remake appears.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-resident-evil-3-remake-demo-analysis">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-resident-evil-3-remake-demo-analysis</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2087194</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 14:13:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>GAME furloughs staff on full pay until end of April</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-13-28/-1585744134046.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088797.jpg" alt=""/><p>GAME has put staff across its business on furlough with full pay until the end of April.</p><p>On 24th March, GAME was forced to close all of its 247 stores after <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-24-uk-government-shuts-down-all-non-essential-shops-as-part-of-measures-to-halt-coronavirus">the government shut all shops selling "non-essential" goods</a>.</p><p>In an email sent last night, 31st March, and seen by Eurogamer, Frasers Group (Mike Ashley's retail business) notified furloughed staff it will pay them their regular pay from 26th March up to 30th April 2020, but it cannot guarantee full pay - or jobs - after the end of April.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-game-furloughs-staff-on-full-pay-until-end-of-april">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-game-furloughs-staff-on-full-pay-until-end-of-april</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088797</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:26:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>There's no No Russian in Russia as Sony Russia refuses Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 Remastered</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-12-06/no-no-russia-in-russia-as-sony-russia-refuses-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered-1585739213260.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088770.jpg" alt=""/><p>
PlayStation Russia has decided not to release Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 Campaign Remastered.</p><p>It means there will be no No Russian - or any other Modern Warfare 2 mission - for PlayStation 4 owners in the country.</p><p>In a statement released last night via Activision's official Call of Duty Russia <a href="https://twitter.com/CallofDutyRU/status/1245036905529475073">Twitter</a> account, the company did not illuminate the reason for PlayStation Russia's disapproval. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-no-no-russia-in-russia-as-sony-russia-refuses-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-no-no-russia-in-russia-as-sony-russia-refuses-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088770</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 12:07:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Xbox Game Pass Ultimate is 50% off</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-11-55/xbox_game_pass_ultimate_deal.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088768.jpg" alt=""/><p>Once again, Microsoft has slashed the price of Xbox Game Pass Ultimate in half by offering a six-month membership for the price of three.</p><p>Both Amazon and Game currently have the promotion live, where a six-month subscription will now set you back £32.99. The way the offer works is you'll be sent two separate three-month codes, so you can use both for yourself or choose to share the spare with a friend if you want. Just be sure to activate it before 14th May 2020.</p><p>For anyone who's heard all this talk about the great value of Game Pass, now's a great chance to get it for an even better price. Even more so now we're locked up indoors looking for more things to do.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-xbox-game-pass-ultimate-deal-50-percent-off">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-xbox-game-pass-ultimate-deal-50-percent-off</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088768</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 11:59:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Infinity Ward brings down the ban hammer on 50k Warzone cheaters</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-11-39/infinity-ward-brings-down-the-ban-hammer-on-50k-warzone-cheaters-1585737565237.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088763.jpg" alt=""/><p>It's been out for less than a month, yet it seems like Call of Duty: Warzone already has a bit of a cheating problem - particularly on PC. A quick browse through the Modern Warfare subreddit will bring up dozens of examples of wall hacking and aimbots. It's prompted some console players to <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CODWarzone/comments/frfulm/time_to_turn_off_cross_play_until_hackers_are/">opt out of cross-play entirely</a> for fear of being lumped in with cheaters on the PC version. Just take a look at the end of one game from the perspective of a hacker, or the person showing off their Warzone hacks on TikTok.  </p><p>The speed at which these hacks have appeared is likely because Warzone is attached to Call of Duty: Modern Warfare - a game that's been out since October last year, giving dubious characters plenty of time to develop hacks. But last night Infinity Ward unveiled further plans to address the problem in Warzone specifically, saying it has a "zero-tolerance" policy towards cheaters, and has been working hard to punish them. </p><p>"We have been enforcing account bans since day one of Warzone's release," explained the <a href="https://blog.activision.com/call-of-duty/2020-03/Cheaters-Not-Welcomed-in-Call-of-Duty-Warzone">blog post</a>. "To date, we [have] issued more than 50k permabans worldwide." </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-infinity-ward-brings-down-the-ban-hammer-on-50k-warzone-cheaters">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-infinity-ward-brings-down-the-ban-hammer-on-50k-warzone-cheaters</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088763</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 11:49:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>You could briefly play Mount &amp; Blade 2: Bannerlord as an actual baby and it was hilarious</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-11-18/you-could-briefly-play-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-as-an-actual-baby-and-it-was-hilarious-1585736321400.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088757.jpg" alt=""/><p>They say seeing the world through the eyes of a child is the purest joy that anyone can experience and in Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord, that's absolutely true.</p><p>This might look like a mod, but it's not.</p><p>After the game launched in Early Access on Monday, players were delighted to discover that pressing 'R' on their keyboards during character creation allowed them, for some reason, to play through this extremely bloody, early medieval RPG as an infant child.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-you-could-briefly-play-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-as-an-actual-baby-and-it-was-hilarious">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-you-could-briefly-play-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-as-an-actual-baby-and-it-was-hilarious</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088757</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 11:38:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Panzer Dragoon: Remake review - flawed revisit to an off-kilter masterpiece</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-09-09/-1585728535193.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088716.jpg" alt=""/><p>Panzer Dragoon is a strange game. Otherworldly would probably be a more elaborate way of putting it: Sega's 1995 original overcame the more limited technology of the Saturn to transport players to a faraway fantasy touched by Frank Herbert's Dune and Hayao Mayazaki's Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind. It's a wonderfully alien place, where oversized insects scuttle under monumental pastel skies. </p><p>No wonder it lodged itself in players' imaginations, gaining a cult status that only seems to have grown in all the years since. There have been follow-ups and spin-offs - the RPG Panzer Dragoon Saga remains an all-time great, while Panzer Dragoon Orta, part of the fantastic wave of Sega games made for Microsoft's first Xbox, provided a muscular modern update and Xbox One launch title Crimson Dragon was a wonky but entertaining spiritual successor from series creator Yukio Futatsugi. This, though, goes back to the source for what is, for better and worse, a faithful retread of the original. </p><p>It's a slightly odd proposition, with Sega and the original development team seemingly uninvolved. Instead this is the work of Polish publisher Forever Entertainment and developer MegaPixel Studio, both relative unknowns - which might be why this feels, more often than not, like a fanmade project, with cut corners and slim production values. But it's important to emphasize the fan part of that equation, because this clearly comes from a place of passion, with the source material being treated with utmost respect. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-panzer-dragoon-remake-review-flawed-revisit-to-an-off-kilter-masterpiece">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-panzer-dragoon-remake-review-flawed-revisit-to-an-off-kilter-masterpiece</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088716</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Someone should make a game about: avoiding quests</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-12-11/-1585653092927.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088559.jpg" alt=""/><p>He's on me before I realise I've been spotted. I curse myself for venturing this close to town but, with supplies running low, what other option was there? Not that keeping to the wilds was any safer - only two days ago I turned around to see three of them barrelling towards me. My pursuer's face filling my field of vision, I brace myself for the inevitable. </p><p>"Greetings, stranger," he says. "Can I interest you in an adventure?"</p><p>Being asked to rescue someone's grandmother from a bandit cave might not sound like nightmare fuel but I've long been fascinated with the idea of dodging quests - ever since The Man With The Long Chin, a character from Teletext gaming mag Digitiser, punched someone for offering him a quest. This comedic revelation opened my mind to a world of possibilities. What if, instead of ending up with a laundry list of unfinished business, you could tell someone to shove their demands right up their Deepwater Hollow? Or, better yet, if you ran a mile whenever anyone looked like they were going to drag you into their affairs?</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-someone-should-make-a-game-about-avoiding-quests">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-someone-should-make-a-game-about-avoiding-quests</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088559</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Valve says Artifact's reboot will no longer let players buy cards or decks</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-04-01-02-22/valve-says-artefacts-reboot-will-no-longer-let-players-buy-cards-or-decks-1585704122732.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088692.jpg" alt=""/><p>It would be fair to say that Valve's digital card game, Artifact, failed to make much of an impact following its <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2018-08-02-valves-new-game-artifact-now-has-a-release-date">high-profile launch</a> at the end of 2018. Mere weeks after its arrival, user numbers had tumbled - and now, after a year of silence, Valve has finally announced a radical overhaul for the game, one that even ditches its fundamental monetisation model of selling cards.</p><p>Designed by Magic: The Gathering creator Richard Garfield, who <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-03-09-concern-for-artifact-as-magic-the-gathering-creator-leaves-valve-amid-layoffs">left Valve last March</a>, Artifact struggled from the off, with players rejecting everything from the game's perceived complexity to balance issues and even its pricing model, which - unlike free-to-play competitors Hearthstone and Gwent - included an upfront cost, alongside payment for additional cards. By the time July came around, Artifact was barely seeing 100 players online in a 24-hour period.</p><p>Valve said little about Artifact for almost year, but suddenly, earlier this month, it began to <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-21-valve-plots-artifact-reboot">tease new activity for the game</a>, saying it would reveal "more news after the launch of Half-Life: Alyx". Now, with Alyx out the door and basking in the light of <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-23-half-life-alyx-review-a-legend-returns-in-elegant-form">rave reviews</a>, Valve has kept its promise, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/games/583950/announcements/detail/2102558993190369211">outlining some early changes</a> for what it's calling Artifact 2.0.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-valve-says-artefacts-reboot-will-no-longer-let-players-buy-cards-or-decks">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-04-01-valve-says-artefacts-reboot-will-no-longer-let-players-buy-cards-or-decks</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088692</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 23:34:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>InXile's post-apocalyptic RPG Wasteland 3 delayed until August</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-23-34/inxiles-post-apocalyptic-rpg-wasteland-3-delayed-until-august-1585694093617.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088681.jpg" alt=""/><p>Wasteland 3, the post-apocalypse-tinged squad-based RPG from developer InXile, will no longer release in May as originally announced, and is now due to arrive in August.</p><p>InXile had originally <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-11-14-post-apocalyptic-rpg-wasteland-3-launches-may-next-year">set a 19th May release date</a> for Wasteland 3 on Xbox One, PS4, and PC, but the developer today announced a new launch date of 28th August, citing the "logistical challenges" arising from coronavirus-related home-working as the reason for the delay.</p><p>"As with most companies, we moved to a work-from-home environment some weeks ago," explained studio head Brian Fargo in a <a href="https://twitter.com/Wasteland/status/1245002745037221896/photo/1">statement posted to Twitter</a>, "and that of course introduced challenges that many of us throughout the world have been learning to manage. We've been excited to see the Wasteland 3 Beta so well received, but the reality is that with these new logistical challenges our release was going to be impacted".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-inxiles-post-apocalyptic-rpg-wasteland-3-delayed-until-august">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-inxiles-post-apocalyptic-rpg-wasteland-3-delayed-until-august</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088681</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 23:05:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Risk of Rain 2 is free to play on Steam this weekend to celebrate a year of early access</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-22-02/risk-of-rain-2-is-free-to-play-on-steam-this-weekend-to-celebrate-a-year-of-early-access-1585688553599.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088676.jpg" alt=""/><p>Risk of Rain 2, developer Hopoo Games' enormously well-received co-operative rogue-like shooter sequel, will be free to play this weekend on Steam, in celebration of its first anniversary and newly released Artifacts 2.0 update.</p><p>Risk of Rain 2 initially entered Steam early access in March last year (a 1.0 release is expected this spring), and Hopoo has been steadily ploughing through its <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-04-26-rogue-like-co-op-shooter-risk-of-rain-2-lays-out-full-early-access-roadmap">extensive early access roadmap</a> ever since. Artifacts 2.0, one of the key milestones on that roadmap, focusses on "long-term content, replayability, and flexibility in the way you play", reintroducing the Artifacts system seen in the original Risk of Rain, albeit with a bit of an additional kick up the bum.</p><p>As you might already be aware, Risk of Rain 2 follows a similar formula to its wonderful predecessor, featuring gloriously chaotic shooting action (this time in full 3D) that grows ever fiercer - bringing tougher, more plentiful enemies - the longer players manage to stay alive. Artifacts serve as a way to amplify that chaos even further, acting as modifiers that can be toggled on or off at the start of each run.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-risk-of-rain-2-is-free-to-play-on-steam-this-weekend-to-celebrate-a-year-of-early-access">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-risk-of-rain-2-is-free-to-play-on-steam-this-weekend-to-celebrate-a-year-of-early-access</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088676</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 21:39:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>This year's 25th anniversary QuakeCon is cancelled due to coronavirus</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-19-38/this-years-25th-anniversary-quakecon-is-cancelled-due-to-the-coronavirus-1585679936314.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088670.jpg" alt=""/><p>Bethesda and id Software have "made the difficult decision" to cancel this year's QuakeCon, which would have marked the 25th anniversary of the event, as a result of the ongoing upheaval caused by the coronavirus pandemic.</p><p>"In recent weeks, we have spent a lot of time discussing how we might still move forward with QuakeCon this year," the companies wrote in a <a href="https://quakecon.bethesda.net">joint statement</a>, "However, with all of the logistical challenges and uncertainties we currently face due to the COVID-19 pandemic, we have made the difficult decision to cancel this year's QuakeCon."</p><p>"The health and safety of our employees, volunteers, vendors, sponsors, and players will always be our top priority, "the statement continued, "and in these times it felt wrong to be talking about a gathering when gathering is the last thing any of us should be doing right now".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-this-years-25th-anniversary-quakecon-is-cancelled-due-to-the-coronavirus">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-this-years-25th-anniversary-quakecon-is-cancelled-due-to-the-coronavirus</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088670</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 19:14:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 Remaster launches tomorrow</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-13-27/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remaster-launches-tomorrow-1585571210406.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088370.jpg" alt=""/><p><strong>UPDATE 31/3/20:</strong> Activision has finally announced Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 Remastered - and it is available now on PlayStation 4. But it is currently <em>only</em> available on PS4, as a timed exclusive.</p><p>PC and Xbox One owners will be able to pre-order the game today, Activision said, but not play it. [UPDATE: Activision has now <a href="https://twitter.com/CallofDuty/status/1245035098992291840">tweeted</a> to say it will become available on "other platforms" on 30th April.]</p><p>On PS4, it is available now from the UK <a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-gb/product/EP0002-CUSA07904_00-CODMW2RSTANDARD1">PlayStation Store</a> priced £19.99.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remaster-launches-tomorrow">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remaster-launches-tomorrow</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088370</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:15:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Minecraft Dungeons gets a May release date on consoles and PC</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-17-44/minecraft-dungeons-gets-a-may-release-date-on-consoles-and-pc-1585673069437.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088651.jpg" alt=""/><p>Minecraft Dungeons - developer Mojang's exceedingly promising, if somewhat leftfield use of the Minecraft brand - will be making its way to Switch, PS4, Xbox One, and PC on 26th May.</p><p>Dungeons, if you've not been keeping an eye on its progress, takes the classic Minecraft aesthetic and fuses it with a top-down dungeon-crawler very much in the vein of Blizzard's classic Diablo series. What follows is an appealing chunk of procedurally generated, co-op focussed monster bashing and treasure hunting for up to four players. </p><p>Despite its family friendly outlook, Dungeons is very much a fully realised take on the dungeon-crawler genre, packed with fearsome (if inevitably angular) enemies from the Minecraft universe, bosses and mini-bosses, oodles of loot, deadly traps, even different combat styles.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-minecraft-dungeons-gets-a-may-release-date-on-consoles-and-pc">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-minecraft-dungeons-gets-a-may-release-date-on-consoles-and-pc</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088651</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 17:42:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fable Anniversary leads Xbox Games with Gold for April</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-16-41/fable-anniversary-and-project-cars-2-lead-xbox-games-with-gold-for-april-1585669270428.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088641.jpg" alt=""/><p>After feeling like the longest month in history, March is nearly over - and frankly we could all do with a pick-me-up. Thankfully Xbox Games with Gold is here to help. </p><p>Next month Xbox Live Gold subscribers can get their hands on Fable Anniversary, the remastered version of the 2004 RPG classic. Players will also be able to access the 2017 game Project Cars 2 by Slightly Mad Studios, and the bundle edition of turn-based RPG Knights of Pen and Paper when it arrives later in the month. Then, if that still hasn't satisfied you, there's Toybox Turbos - the 2014 racing game by Codemasters. </p><p>It's worth noting each game is only available for a limited time: Project Cars 2 between April 1st-30th, Knights of Pen and Paper from 16th April to 15th May, Fable Anniversary from 1st-15th April, and Toybox Turbos from 16th-30th April. Still no word on a release date for <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2018-01-17-sources-microsoft-plots-fable-return">Fable 4</a>, though. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-fable-anniversary-and-project-cars-2-lead-xbox-games-with-gold-for-april">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-fable-anniversary-and-project-cars-2-lead-xbox-games-with-gold-for-april</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088641</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:46:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord claims biggest Steam launch of year so far</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-16-37/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-claims-biggest-steam-launch-of-year-so-far-1585669016202.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088640.jpg" alt=""/><p>
Almost eight years after it was first announced, Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord finally arrived via Steam Early Access yesterday.</p><p>The medieval action role-player is doing well, too. Developer Taleworlds has trumpeted some impressive concurrent player numbers - enough, it says, to make it Steam's biggest launch this year.</p><p>These numbers have only grown over the past day, with upwards of 200,000 people now playing at the time of writing.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-claims-biggest-steam-launch-of-year-so-far">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-claims-biggest-steam-launch-of-year-so-far</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088640</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:39:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Gamescom isn't cancelled, yet - but it will hold &quot;significantly expanded&quot; digital show</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-16-21/-1585668061488.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088634.jpg" alt=""/><p>Gamescom will scale up its digital portion this year with a "significantly expanded" Opening Night Live announcement show. </p><p>The event's "Gamescom now" streaming schedule, which features demos and interviews with developers, will also be ramped up. </p><p>As for the physical show - which last year welcomed a staggering 373,000 people to Cologne's cramped convention centre - organisers said today that no final decision has yet been made. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-gamescom-to-significantly-expand-digital-elements">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-gamescom-to-significantly-expand-digital-elements</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088634</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:17:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fortnite adds bullet-blocking Kingsman umbrellas</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-15-28/fortnite-adds-bullet-blocking-kingsman-umbrellas-1585664906694.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088610.jpg" alt=""/><p>Another update, another week without patch notes - but it seems v12.30 has a couple of surprises in store for players, as two new items have been introduced.</p><p>Continuing this season's spy theme, Kingsman umbrellas are now available as legendary items in the game. Presumably these are based on the Kingsman comic and film series, particularly the scene in which Harry uses an umbrella to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tukQDg22o9M">deck a bunch of thugs in a pub</a> - and similarly, the item seems to be fairly useful in Fortnite too. You can use it to dart forwards, smash things, hit other players, and even block bullets (for a short amount of time). Like a very dapper riot shield. </p><p>The umbrellas even briefly work as a glider, but this has been causing problems for some players, who clearly assumed it would stay open for longer than three seconds. An easy mistake to make, given it looks very similar to Fortnite's famous victory umbrella gliders. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-fortnite-adds-bullet-blocking-kingsman-umbrellas">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-fortnite-adds-bullet-blocking-kingsman-umbrellas</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088610</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:32:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>BAFTA Game Awards nominees all discounted in the latest Humble sale</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-15-11/sekiro_bafta_humble_sale.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088612.jpg" alt=""/><p>A number of nominees in this year's BAFTA Game Awards are now on sale at the Humble Store.</p><p>Frustratingly, it's a bit of a mixed bag in terms of good offers. Some prices, including those for Sekiro and Control, are the lowest we've seen for those games so far on PC. Others you'll find for cheaper elsewhere if you do a quick scout around.</p><p>I've put some of the key offers and prices below, but you can find everything (and maybe even a few hidden gems) on the full <a href="https://www.humblebundle.com/store/promo/bafta-game-awards-sale?partner=eurogamer" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">BAFTA Game Awards Humble sale</a> page.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-bafta-game-awards-nominees-all-discounted-in-the-latest-humble-sale">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-bafta-game-awards-nominees-all-discounted-in-the-latest-humble-sale</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088612</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Outer Worlds lands on Nintendo Switch in June</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-14-40/-1585662022083.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088599.jpg" alt=""/><p>
Sci-fi role-player The Outer Worlds will arrive for Nintendo Switch as a physical release and digital download on 5th June.</p><p>Boxed copies will include a physical cartridge - but also a sizeable download, as has rather become the norm. You'll need space to fit a 6GB download, described as a "day one patch". </p><p>The game's Nintendo Switch price point has been set at £50/&#8364;60.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-the-outer-worlds-lands-on-nintendo-switch-in-june">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-the-outer-worlds-lands-on-nintendo-switch-in-june</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088599</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 14:44:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Granblue Fantasy: Versus review: a new step for fighting games with old failings.</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-12-18/granblue-fantasy-vs-review-1585653507400.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088550.jpg" alt=""/><p>There's a widely held belief that fighting games are hard to get into. That their steep learning curve, niche appeal and high skill ceiling are just too much to swallow. Arc System Works, developer of both the hardcore Guilty Gear and the more accessible Dragon Ball Fighterz, has come up with a sweetener with Granblue Fantasy Vs. As an adaptation of a super popular mobile JRPG and created by arguably the best producers of fighting games today, Granblue has the potential to be truly stellar. Is this the fighting game for those who struggle to find enjoyment in the genre - or is it simply more of the same?</p><p>Starting with the roster, Granblue Fantasy Vs has a pretty shallow pool of 12 characters to pick from. If there's a silver lining to that slim selection, though, it's that the diversity of fighting game archetypes is surprisingly large. You've got everything from your classic fireball and uppercut fighters, long distance oppressors, and grapplers, alongside a myriad of others with vastly different play-styles. This character diversity comes hand in hand with the appearance of each character, as all of them seem to fill a wide range of tastes. Are you a tad edgy? Vaseraga is for you! You like things basic and simple? Gran is the most vanilla of protagonists you'll find all year. This lack of overlapping looks and fighting styles should ensure you'll find someone you enjoy.</p><p>If there's one aspect that the characters - and everything else for that matter - have in common, it's that they're all damn gorgeous. I can't imagine how much work it must have taken the artists at Arc System Works to achieve the aesthetic of Granblue, but all that effort shows. The beautifully animated 3D fighters pop out from the background and rarely get lost regardless of how detailed the stage is, their movements are smooth, and every attack looks as though it has some serious force to it, while stages range from high-fantasy villages with castles jutting upwards behind the buildings, to sweeping wildernesses. Granblue Fantasy Vs is eye candy of the highest calibre.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-granblue-fantasy-vs-review">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-granblue-fantasy-vs-review</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088550</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>One Step from Eden is bullet-hell meets Slay the Spire, and it's divine</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-12-07/-1585652833097.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088554.jpg" alt=""/><p>What do you get if you mix a bullet-hell shooter with a deck-building game like Slay the Spire? You get One Step from Eden, and it is a revelation.</p><p>So much is like Slay the Spire. You have only one life to see how far you can get. You choose cards to add after battle. You choose between different paths to follow. There are bosses, mini-bosses, and things to do other than battle (rescue people, visit the shop, etc). You buy, sell, remove, and upgrade cards. You gain experience which goes towards unlocking new cards and characters. You even progress  towards something - Eden in this case, not up a spire. </p><p>But at the same time it's incredibly different. In One Step from Eden, <em>you move</em>. You play on a grid - you on one side, enemies on the other - and you need to move around to line up your abilities while dodging what your opponents throw at you.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-one-step-from-eden-is-bullet-hell-meets-slay-the-spire-and-its-divine">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-one-step-from-eden-is-bullet-hell-meets-slay-the-spire-and-its-divine</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088554</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 12:26:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fan-made Animal Crossing site makes sharing designs easy</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-11-50/fan-made-animal-crossing-site-makes-it-easy-to-find-designs-1585651806227.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088551.jpg" alt=""/><p>You're a few days in, the Able Sisters have set up shop, and it's time to get some fancy threads in your Animal Crossing: New Horizons town. But where can you find new custom designs?</p><p>If you want to download some lovely designs into your game, chances are you'll be looking through Twitter and <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ACQR/">Reddit</a> for ideas. New Horizons allows players to upload their work and share it via codes - but there's no official database either in-game or online allowing players to browse through everything and select designs they like. So, naturally, a fan is here to help. </p><p>Last night Reddit user plump_tomato <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AnimalCrossing/comments/fru6st/im_working_on_a_database_for_custom_designs_for/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;utm_name=iossmf">shared their work-in-progress database</a> called <a href="https://nookpedia.com/designs">Nookpedia</a>, and it's already received a significant amount of attention. Users can upload screenshots of their codes and name their designs so other users can find them with the search bar and filters. And, if you want a complete lucky dip, you can simply browse through the custom design pages until you find something you like. I've already spotted several stylish Mulan pieces, and contributed my own Fire Emblem: Three Houses Dimitri cosplay. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-fan-made-animal-crossing-site-makes-it-easy-to-find-designs">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-fan-made-animal-crossing-site-makes-it-easy-to-find-designs</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088551</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 12:02:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Yes, Call of Duty's most infamous level is still in Modern Warfare 2 Remastered</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-11-54/no-russian-in-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered-1585652091513.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088549.jpg" alt=""/><p>Activision has yet to officially announce its Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 remaster, and yet footage of the entire game is now readily available to watch online. </p><p>It includes the mission No Russian - the series' most infamous level where you can massacre civilians in an airport terminal while posing as an undercover terrorist. </p><p>As Eurogamer reported yesterday, <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remaster-launches-tomorrow">Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2: Campaign Remastered launches today</a>, at least on PlayStation 4. And while it's not yet available to download, copies are clearly already out in the wild. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-no-russian-in-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-no-russian-in-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2-remastered</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088549</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 11:53:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>More details emerge on Nintendo's Mario remasters</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-10-47/-1585648067106.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088529.jpg" alt=""/><p>After an initial leak set the floodgates open yesterday, new details have been published on how Nintendo's upcoming array of Mario games old and new will actually be released. </p><p>There's a little more, too, on the Switch's new Paper Mario game, which has yet to be announced by Nintendo itself. </p><p><a href="https://venturebeat.com/2020/03/30/nintendo-is-making-3d-mario-remasters-for-his-35th-anniversary/">Venturebeat</a> reported that the three 3D Mario remasters would be offered in a collection, dubbed something like "Super Mario All-Stars 2". This is branding Eurogamer has heard of being used internally. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-more-details-emerge-on-nintendos-mario-remasters">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-more-details-emerge-on-nintendos-mario-remasters</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088529</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 11:01:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Good Job review - a proper little delight</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-10-07/-1585645657804.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088517.jpg" alt=""/><p>I have waited so many years to hear the right words. So many years, not even knowing what the right words are, or what form they will take. Now I have heard them: Deliver a Big Cube. Okay, not the exact words I was expecting, but they will do. They will do nicely.</p><p>
At the start, it's a small cube. A small cube of pink space-jelly or something, lurid and wibbling in a lab. I pick it up and drag it. Its flesh, to quote General Sternwood, is too much like the flesh of men. It squidges along the floor behind me. Just an office worker taking a cube for a stroll. </p><p>But when I run over pools of pink goo, the cube starts to draw them up. It starts to get bigger! More pink goo! I need more! I start to hunt it down, clumsy now because my small cube is no longer a small cube, and is actually fairly awkward in fact. Walls shatter. Wheely chairs go flying. Equipment is upturned. No matter! The cube drinks. Eventually I find a vat of the goo stuff - three storeys high. Turn the valve, plug in a pipe, let it spill everywhere! The cube erupts into its final size, a true monster. But still so light and jelly-like to drag. Into the weighing machine and off to whoever requested a big cube. Delivered, mate. I hope they love it as much as I did.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-good-job-review-a-proper-little-delight">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-good-job-review-a-proper-little-delight</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088517</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 10:02:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Get up to £30 off Fnatic's excellent gaming keyboards on Amazon today</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-12-14/three-top-rated-mechanical-keyboards-are-discounted-on-amazon-today-1585566870514.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088316.jpg" alt=""/><p>
    <strong>While some models have sold out, many are still available as of Tuesday! </strong>
  </p><p>Fnatic is one of the top esports organisations in the world, but they're also the makers of a surprisingly robust line of gaming accessories including mice, headsets and keyboards. Today a number of their mechanical keyboards are discounted on Amazon, including our picks for the <a href="https://eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-best-mechanical-keyboard-for-gaming-typing-coding-7008#quiet">best mechanical keyboard for gaming</a> and the <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-best-mechanical-keyboard-for-gaming-typing-coding-7008#value">best value mechanical keyboard for gaming</a>.</p><p>If you're after a new keyboard to make spending time indoors a more pleasant experience, whether you're writing up reports, working on an essay or blasting demons in Doom Eternal, these are a great option. Here are all of the discounted keyboards involved in the sale, plus a quick primer on why we rate them so highly.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-03-30-three-top-rated-mechanical-keyboards-are-discounted-on-amazon-today">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-03-30-three-top-rated-mechanical-keyboards-are-discounted-on-amazon-today</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088316</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 10:02:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Persona 5 Royal review - both better and worse than the original</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-07-32/persona-5-royal-review-1585636377963.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088443.jpg" alt=""/><p>It's a great intro: protagonist Joker darting along the casino roof, quick like a shadow. Making fast work of a handful of enemies while leaving others in the dust, his black coat swishing behind him. The excited voices of his team mates over the intercom as he's almost reached his goal, but then! Curse your sudden but inevitable betrayal! He's surrounded!</p><p>The first sequence of Persona 5 Royal acts as foreshadowing and tutorial all wrapped up in one, showing you everything you will regularly be doing in each dungeon you crawl through - jumping between platforms and squeezing through ducts to find a way forward, hiding away from enemies or ambushing them when they're not looking. Most importantly, in round-based combat you unleash Persona, manifestations of parts of Joker's psyche who can use different elemental attacks, healing spells and stat buffs. Persona 5 Royal also adds a grappling hook to your arsenal, which you'll mostly use to find shortcuts and additional treasure.</p><p>Joker and his friends, regular students at Shujin Academy in Tokyo, one day stumble into the Metaverse, a parallel reality that manifests Palaces where people live out their worst desires. There's also Mementos, a sprawling maze of randomly generated dungeons. The group of high schoolers enter these palaces to steal people's treasures, causing them to let go of harmful desires and confess their crimes.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-persona-5-royal-review">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-persona-5-royal-review</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088443</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Now modders are using Half-Life: Alyx to get Half-Life 2 working in VR</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-31-02-40/now-fans-are-using-half-life-alyx-to-get-half-life-2-working-in-vr-1585618803603.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088480.jpg" alt=""/><p>Last week, the Half-Life community's attempts to translate Valve's new VR extravaganza, Half-Life: Alyx, to the flat screen showed <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-27-heres-a-look-at-half-life-alyx-being-played-without-vr">very early promise</a>. And this week, another portion of Half-Life fandom is approaching the problem in something like the opposite direction, attempting to turn the seminal, and distinctly non-VR, Half-Life 2 into a VR game, using Alyx as its foundation.</p><p>This isn't the first attempt to translate Half-Life 2 into VR, of course - an <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2017-05-12-modders-set-out-to-make-half-life-2-playable-on-rift-and-vive">extensive VR overhaul</a>, promising to deliver "updated effects, textures, models &amp; maps" reemerged in 2017, having started life four years earlier - but this latest effort takes a rather different approach, porting Valve's original game into Alyx's VR-enabled Source 2 engine.</p><p>One enterprising modder, known as Vect0R (who's also spend time digging up unused Half-Life 2 content and producing a real-time raytracing mod for the game), has made enough progress - converting map files and assets to Source 2's format and adding them to Alyx - to be able to <a href="https://youtu.be/da6y6-in29k">show off</a> a little bit of a VR shooty-bang-bang run around a very old-school City 17.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-now-fans-are-using-half-life-alyx-to-get-half-life-2-working-in-vr">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-31-now-fans-are-using-half-life-alyx-to-get-half-life-2-working-in-vr</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088480</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Steam making changes to reduce bandwidth usage during coronavirus outbreak</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-23-34/valve-making-changes-to-reduce-steam-bandwidth-usage-during-coronavirus-outbreak-1585607681037.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088479.jpg" alt=""/><p>Valve has made some adjustments to the way Steam currently deals with game downloads in order to reduce bandwidth usage during the coronavirus outbreak.</p><p>"We know a lot of you (like us here at Valve) are stuck at home right now trying to work or attend school remotely," the company <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/games/593110/announcements/detail/2074411495515541376">wrote</a>, "Or maybe you're just playing a bunch of great games on Steam. Whatever the case may be, we know that with so many people at home trying to get things done at the same time, it can put a stress on your home's internet bandwidth."</p><p>With that in mind, Steam will now prioritise and schedule game auto-updates slightly differently to normal for the foreseeable future.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-steam-making-changes-to-reduce-bandwidth-usage-during-coronavirus-outbreak">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-steam-making-changes-to-reduce-bandwidth-usage-during-coronavirus-outbreak</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088479</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 23:26:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Unintentional Star Wars: Jedi Academy cross-play lets PC players wreak havoc on console</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-20-51/star-wars-jedi-academy-pc-players-wreaking-havoc-on-console-thanks-to-unintentional-cross-play-1585597892518.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088462.jpg" alt=""/><p>Players dipping their toes into Star Wars: Jedi Academy for the first time over the weekend, following Thursday's PS4 and Switch release, have come up against an unexpected obstacle in their quest for Jedi supremacy; long-time PC players are intentionally invading console games to wreak nefarious havoc, thanks to a seemingly unintentional cross-play feature.</p><p>Star Wars: Jedi Academy initially launched for PC all the way back in 2003, giving players on the platform a massive 17 years head-start in which to hone their lightsaber skills. Throw in the mouse and keyboard advantage of PC, and players of the freshly launched console ports (as <a href="https://www.pcgamer.com/uk/accidental-crossplay-between-star-wars-jedi-academy-on-pc-and-console-is-a-slaughter/">spotted by PC Gamer</a>) weren't exactly thrilled when they ventured into Jedi Academy's multiplayer mode this weekend, only to be utterly obliterated by invaders from the dark side.</p><p>"I was excited to play this game online, so I picked it up immediately", wrote a clearly disappointed <a href="https://www.resetera.com/threads/jedi-academy-console-rerelease-seemingly-has-unintentional-cross-play-with-pc-users.177788/">May Payment on Resetera</a>, "I joined a game where 1 player was absolutely mopping the floor with us and he had .twitchtv in his username. Sure enough, I looked him up and he was playing on PC in a switch server absolutely decimating everyone."</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-unintentional-star-wars-jedi-academy-cross-play-lets-pc-players-wreak-havoc-on-console">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-unintentional-star-wars-jedi-academy-cross-play-lets-pc-players-wreak-havoc-on-console</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088462</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 20:25:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Pokémon Go will let you raid with friends from home</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-18-57/pokemon-go-will-let-you-raid-with-friends-from-home-1585591060647.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088445.jpg" alt=""/><p>In its most fundamental change to gameplay yet, Pokémon Go will soon allow you to take part in raid battles with friends from home. </p><p>The change is one of several new features in development at Niantic in response to the global coronavirus crisis, detailed today in a lengthy <a href="https://nianticlabs.com/blog/stay-safe/" target="_blank">blog post</a> from company founder John Hanke. </p><p>The post also touched on the game's annual Go Fest events, which see tens of thousands of players meet up in cities every summer. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-pokemon-go-will-let-you-raid-with-friends-from-home">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-pokemon-go-will-let-you-raid-with-friends-from-home</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088445</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 18:58:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Riot's first-person tactical shooter Valorant gets closed beta next week</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-18-31/riots-first-person-tactical-shooter-valorant-gets-closed-beta-next-week-1585589472492.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088437.jpg" alt=""/><p>Valorant, the new free-to-play first-person tactical shooter from League of Legends developer Riot Games, will be entering closed beta next week, ahead of its launch on PC this summer.</p><p>Originally announced under the name Project A as part of <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-10-16-heres-everything-riots-announced-so-far-for-league-of-legends-10-year-anniversary">Riot's tenth anniversary celebrations</a> last year, Valorant is a character-based shooter, with a focus on tactical play, inspired by the likes of Counter-Strike: Global Offensive, Crossfire, and, yes, Overwatch.</p><p>It's a five-versus-five affair - each playable Agent having their own distinct abilities - in which the attacking team attempts to plant a bomb (the "Spike") behind enemy lines. The  defending team, meanwhile, must attempt defuse it or simply last the course of a round in order to win.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-riots-first-person-tactical-shooter-valorant-gets-closed-beta-next-week">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-riots-first-person-tactical-shooter-valorant-gets-closed-beta-next-week</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088437</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 18:03:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Resident Evil 3 remake review - at times brilliant, but not a patch on its predecessor</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-15-30/resident-evil-3-remake-review-at-times-brilliant-but-not-a-patch-on-its-predecessor-1585578657183.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088398.jpg" alt=""/><p>The Resident Evil 3 remake comes out just over a year after the Resident Evil 2 remake, which is particularly satisfying timing when you consider the original Resident Evil 3: Nemesis came out just a year after Resident Evil 2, back in 1999. Resident Evil 3 launched just before the launch of the PlayStation 2 and a transition to the next-generation of consoles, and the Resident Evil 3 remake launches not long before the release of the PS5 and Xbox Series X - another satisfying parallel. But unfortunately there is an unwelcome parallel: the Resident Evil 3 remake, like the original upon which it is based, is inferior to its predecessor.</p><p>Don't get me wrong, when the Resident Evil 3 remake is good, it's fantastic. The remodelled Jill Valentine, if not inspired by Milla Jovovich then certainly developed with the Resident Evil movie star in mind, is a wonderful character. Her desperate attempt to escape Raccoon City with the relentless Nemesis monster on her back quickly turns into a save the city operation - she's likeable, determined and I couldn't help but root for her throughout.</p><p>I was surprised to find myself rooting for Umbrella mercenary Carlos Oliveira, too - once I got over his spectacularly vibrant bouffant hair. Carlos comes across as, well, a bit of a dick when he saves Jill - early doors - from the clutches of Nemesis. But as the story progresses so does his character. In reworking Resident Evil 3's plot, Capcom has placed greater emphasis on Carlos, and you play as him in two extended portions of the game. Jill is of course the star of the show here, but Carlos benefits from the extra quality time - and his new hairdo, which I'm convinced has a life of its own.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-resident-evil-3-remake-review-at-times-brilliant-but-not-a-patch-on-its-predecessor">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-resident-evil-3-remake-review-at-times-brilliant-but-not-a-patch-on-its-predecessor</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088398</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Sources: Nintendo Switch 2020 line-up dominated by Mario games old and new</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-15-29/-1585578540702.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088405.jpg" alt=""/><p>Nintendo Switch's first-party line-up for the rest of 2020 will be dominated by Mario games old and new, to coincide with the original Super Mario Bros.' 35th anniversary.</p><p>That's according to Eurogamer sources with knowledge of Nintendo's upcoming plans, who have corroborated a report posted by <a href="https://www.videogameschronicle.com/news/super-mario-bros-35th-anniversary/">VGC</a>.</p><p>First, the report states Nintendo will release "most of Super Mario's 35-year back catalogue this year, remastered for Nintendo Switch".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-sources-nintendo-switch-2020-line-up-dominated-by-mario-games-old-and-new">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-sources-nintendo-switch-2020-line-up-dominated-by-mario-games-old-and-new</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088405</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 15:39:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Doom Eternal on Stadia looks great - but the lag is just too high</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-10-16/digitalfoundry-2020-doom-eternal-stadia-looks-the-part-but-lag-is-too-high-1585559817331.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088310.jpg" alt=""/><p>id Software's Doom Eternal is one of the best-looking shooters ever made. Powered by the id Tech 7 engine, the game delivers even higher resolution textures, more complex environments and a tight lock on its target 60 frames per second. It's also built from the ground up for the Vulkan low-level graphics API, meaning that in theory, it's a match made in heaven for Google's Stadia - a system that focuses on Linux and Vulkan for its technological backbone. However, after putting some time into the game, it's disappointing overall - at the most basic level, lag makes the Doom Eternal experience a good deal worse than any other platform.</p><p>There are advantages though, of course. Taking Xbox One X as an example, you have a 41GB download to get through before you can pick up your controllers. Stadia's cloud-based set-up means that the process of getting your hands on the game is instantaneous. But in the case of Doom Eternal, that's where the plus points for gaming at Stadia come to an end.</p><p>In assessing this port, we're pursuing our usual strategy of running the game with the best quality set-up. That means we're using the Stadia controller connected directly to Google's servers via WiFi, with imagery delivered via Chromecast Ultra to an LG OLED B8, rated for 22ms of lag under Game Mode. A 300mbps Virgin Media fibre connection, with the Chromecast attached via Ethernet removes any home WiFi-related latency that might occur, while our lag measurements were carried out with no other devices sharing the line. Pulling up the Stadia connection tab, our set-up is rated as excellent with 4K enabled. Despite this, there are still some minor, very infrequent stutters in performance. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-doom-eternal-stadia-looks-the-part-but-lag-is-too-high">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-doom-eternal-stadia-looks-the-part-but-lag-is-too-high</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088310</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Police stop Stevenage man playing Pokémon Go while driving</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-14-33/-1585575195082.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088385.jpg" alt=""/><p>
Police have pulled over a man driving around Stevenage, Hertfordshire, playing Pokémon Go during the coronavirus lockdown.</p><p>When asked the reason for his car journey, the man told coppers he was out catching Pokémon, <a href="https://www.itv.com/news/anglia/2020-03-29/police-stop-driver-playing-pokemon-go-in-stevenage-during-coronavirus-lockdown/">ITV News</a> reported. </p><p>Police officers informed the man this was "not essential travel" and directed him home.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-police-stop-stevenage-man-playing-pokemon-go-while-driving">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-police-stop-stevenage-man-playing-pokemon-go-while-driving</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088385</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 14:47:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Nvidia teams up with Minecraft creators to show off new ray-traced worlds</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-13-50/nvidia-teams-up-with-minecraft-creators-to-create-new-worlds-technical-guides-1585572612465.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088366.jpg" alt=""/><p>While hardware-accelerated ray tracing was first demonstrated by Nvidia with <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2018-08-20-nvidia-unveil-rtx-2070-rtx-2080-and-rtx-2080-ti-at-gamescom-7006">modern games like Battlefield 5 and Metro Exodus</a>, where RT lights or shadows are used alongside traditional rasterised graphics, completely ray-traced versions of games have also been developed to stunning effect. From early demonstrations of path tracing in Minecraft via <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5jD0mELZPD8">Sonic Ether's RT shader mod</a> to the <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2019-quake-2-rtx-version-one-point-two-upgrade">release of Quake 2 RTX</a>, we've seen a series of old-school titles reborn with modern techniques, in a way that seems perfectly suited to demonstrating the unique capabilities of RT technology. Today, we get a fresh look at the most highly-anticipated ray tracing showcase: Minecraft with RTX. </p><p>It's important to note that this is the official Microsoft release of Minecraft with ray tracing, a near total overhaul of the game, rather than the shader mod that preceded it. We first went <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2019-hands-on-with-minecraft-rtx-path-tracing"> went hands-on with the title at Gamescom 2019</a>, and since then we also got an <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-inside-xbox-series-x-full-specs">exclusive look at the Minecraft DXR tech demo on Xbox Series X</a>. While the game doesn't yet have a release date, some Minecraft creators have already gotten access to development builds - and today we're seeing the fruits of their labours for the first time.</p><p>First, here are screenshots of three worlds created by Minecraft mainstays, with Nvidia's descriptions. You can click the image to see the full-size, full-fat screenshot in all its glory.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-03-30-nvidia-teams-up-with-minecraft-creators-to-create-new-worlds-technical-guides">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2020-03-30-nvidia-teams-up-with-minecraft-creators-to-create-new-worlds-technical-guides</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088366</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>As Riot bids to take on Blizzard and Valve, the studio faces challenges of its own making</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-09-57/as-riot-bids-to-take-on-blizzard-and-valve-the-studio-faces-challenges-of-its-own-making-1585558651633.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2087852.jpg" alt=""/><p>For a good decade, Blizzard Entertainment has been the undisputed champion of developing and publishing prestige PC games. Warcraft, World of Warcraft, StarCraft, Overwatch, Diablo, and Hearthstone (we can maybe skip Heroes of the Storm, sorry) have sat at more or less the top of their respective genres for years. In some cases, decades. Blizzard was way ahead of the curve in setting up, in Battle.net, a kind of storefront-launcher across its multiple games. It has an annual convention, in BlizzCon, where thousands gather to cosplay as their favourite Blizzard characters and cheer the most minuscule of announcements. Most of all, it's one of the only developer-publishers whose name carries the same kind of "seal of quality" weight that you could apply to the likes of Nintendo. But things change, and a new challenger approaches. A plucky, independent little studio called Riot Games fancies a pop at the title.</p><p>The background here is really quite delicious, too. For the unfamiliar, back in 2002 Blizzard released the popular, influential real-time strategy game Warcraft 3, and then in 2003 some modders came along and made a new mode of their own for it called Defence of the Ancients, a kind of weird tower defense evolution of the RTS (and they actually made it with the official world editor which is why, you'd imagine, Blizzard was so aggressive with its terms and conditions in the recent Warcraft 3: Reforged). After the Defence of the Ancients mod gained huge popularity, rival company Valve bought the rights to it - much to Blizzard's chagrin - and hired one of the mod's major developers, the pseudonymous "IceFrog", to make Dota 2 for them in 2009. Another designer of the mod, Steve "Guinsoo" Feak, who worked on it even before IceFrog, went on to join Riot's co-founders - a couple of ambitious, business school dorm-buddies called Marc Merrill and Brandon Beck - and made League of Legends.</p><p>Now, Dota 2 is handing out <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-08-25-og-becomes-first-team-ever-to-win-the-internationals-massive-prize-pool-twice">prizes in the tens of millions</a> to its tournament winners and Valve of course has a near total monopoly on the PC gaming storefront. Riot's League of Legends is frequently the most-watched game on Twitch, is probably the biggest esport in the world, and probably the biggest game in the world too. As of August 2019, League is averaging peaks of <em>eight million</em> concurrent players worldwide. Meanwhile, at Blizzard, the remaster of Warcraft 3 launched to <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-01-30-warcraft-3-reforged-houses-a-fantastic-rts-but-blizzard-has-fluffed-the-remake">criticism</a> and <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-02-02-warcraft-3-reforged-is-the-lowest-user-scored-game-on-metacritic">controversy</a>, the RTS as a genre is in the worst shape it's ever been, and the company is still getting over the huge protests from both fans and its own staff for the handling of Ng Wai Chung, or "<a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-10-08-blizzard-punishes-hearthstone-pro-for-voicing-hong-kong-support">Blitzchung</a>" - one of its own professional players.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-as-riot-bids-to-take-on-blizzard-and-valve-the-studio-faces-challenges-of-its-own-making">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-as-riot-bids-to-take-on-blizzard-and-valve-the-studio-faces-challenges-of-its-own-making</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2087852</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 12:04:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Last Oasis pulled offline days after rocky launch</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-11-22/-1585563770988.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088330.jpg" alt=""/><p>
Post-apocalyptic survival MMO Last Oasis is going offline for up to a week, after a launch marred by server issues left many unable to play. </p><p>Last Oasis debuted via Steam Early Access last Thursday, 26th March, but was quickly beset by server issues. Players reported being unable to load into the game due to severe wait times and server crashes. The few who did get in, however, reported the game itself a fun experience. </p><p>In a video post to Twitter last night, developer Donkey Crew announced the game would now be taken offline. All owners are eligible for "no questions asked" refund.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-last-oasis-pulled-offline-days-after-rocky-launch">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-last-oasis-pulled-offline-days-after-rocky-launch</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088330</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 11:17:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Long-running Official Xbox Magazine shuts down</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-10-19/-1585559985792.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088312.jpg" alt=""/><p>The Official Xbox Magazine has closed down, Eurogamer has learnt.</p><p>OXM folded last week, with the magazine's last few remaining staff let go. Eurogamer understands OXM is one of six magazines closed at Bath-based media company Future, although it is the only gaming magazine among them.</p><p>The closure of OXM comes in the same year Microsoft plans to release its next console, the Xbox Series X. Just one day ago the OXM Twitter account advertised an OXM subscription.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-long-running-official-xbox-magazine-shuts-down">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-long-running-official-xbox-magazine-shuts-down</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088312</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 10:23:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Final Fantasy 7 Remake street date broken as Square Enix issues release warning</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-28-15-02/final-fantasy-7-remake-street-date-broken-as-square-enix-issues-release-date-warning-1585407773314.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088191.jpg" alt=""/><p><strong>ORIGINAL STORY 28/3/20:</strong> Final Fantasy 7 Remake publisher Square Enix has asked fans not to spoil the game, as it acknowledged copies would likely turn up early in Europe and Australia.</p><p>The first began appearing over the weekend, as we reported below. Now, a new statement from the publisher has explained this is because it deliberately shipped them early amid the ongoing disruption caused by the coronavirus, to ensure they reached fans by release date.</p><p>"Our highest priority is that all of you, including those who live in countries currently facing the biggest disruption, can play the game at launch, so we made the decision to ship the game far earlier than usual to Europe and Australia.</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-28-final-fantasy-7-remake-street-date-broken-as-square-enix-issues-release-date-warning">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-28-final-fantasy-7-remake-street-date-broken-as-square-enix-issues-release-date-warning</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088191</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 10:01:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>If you're jonesing for some more Fire Emblem-esque action, Langrisser has you covered</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-30-07-34/if-youre-jonesing-for-some-more-fire-emblem-esque-action-langrisser-has-you-covered-1585550071030.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088244.jpg" alt=""/><p>I'm not going to pretend to have played Langrisser games in their 90s heyday, though I will admit to being <em>vaguely</em> familiar with them. They're the epitome of 16-bit exotica, with only the 1991 original making its way out of Japan, and even then only doing so in North America and under the not-quite-so-striking title Warsong. After that the series remained in the east, where it built up a reputation as a solid alternative on Sega's platforms to Nintendo's burgeoning Fire Emblem series. </p><p>Given the rise in popularity of Fire Emblem in recent years - and especially after last year's breakout hit Three Houses introduced a whole new audience to the appeal of strategy RPGs - it makes perfect sense that publisher NISA and developer Chara-Ani would try and repeat the trick with Langrisser, and the recently-released remakes of original developer Masaya's first two games does a fine job of it too. This is a luscious package, presented with care and thought. </p><p>And they present two very robust takes on the genre, admirably untouched by more modern concerns. Which is a polite way of saying these are two very old school takes on the genre, with few of the flourishes you find in contemporary Fire Emblem - something which I'm sure many will take as a blessing. There's no tending to a curriculum, or taking time out for tea - this is purely the <em>serious</em> business of battle (although it's worth nothing that Langrisser 2 does introduce branching paths in its story). </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-if-youre-jonesing-for-some-more-fire-emblem-esque-action-langrisser-has-you-covered">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-30-if-youre-jonesing-for-some-more-fire-emblem-esque-action-langrisser-has-you-covered</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088244</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rhianna Pratchett's Lost Words: Beyond the Page is out now if you have Stadia</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-18-17/-1585502249016.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088243.jpg" alt=""/><p>Lost Words: Beyond the Page - an "emotionally moving, fully-voiced" platformer written by Tomb Raider reboot writer Rhianna Pratchett - is out now, and it's exclusive to Google Stadia for one year.</p><p>Whilst we haven't seen a lot of the game in the lead up to release, we did find out last month that the game would be <a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-02-18-stadia-adds-support-for-samsung-phones-this-week">exclusive to the streaming platform</a> Stadia. This means you won't see it on Steam until at least March 2021.</p><p>"'Stadia First' - what does this means for other platforms? Steam shows plain 2020," a commenter asked Modus Games on Twitter a few weeks back (thanks, <a href="https://www.pcgamer.com/uk/tomb-raider-writer-rhianna-pratchetts-new-game-is-out-today-exclusively-on-stadia/">PC Gamer</a>), to which the publisher replied: "It will be exclusive to Stadia for the first year."</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-rhianna-pratchetts-lost-words-beyond-the-page-is-out-now-if-you-have-stadia">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-rhianna-pratchetts-lost-words-beyond-the-page-is-out-now-if-you-have-stadia</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088243</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 18:21:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>GameStop is closing another 300+ stores this year</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-17-38/-1585499889397.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088240.jpg" alt=""/><p>US specialist retailer, GameStop, has confirmed it's closing at least 320 stores over the next 12 months.</p><p>The company has already closed 321 stores as part of restructuring efforts in the financial year ending February 2020, and now a similar number of its 5,500 stores are expected to shut by the end of this financial year, too. </p><p>The closures come in spite of the company reporting a net income of $21 million (£16.8 million) at the end of the last financial year. </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-gamestop-is-closing-another-300-stores-this-year">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-gamestop-is-closing-another-300-stores-this-year</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088240</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:35:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>These latest Fortnite glitches almost guarantee a win</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-16-55/-1585497329334.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088236.jpg" alt=""/><p>Two new glitches have popped up in Fortnite - one is making players invisible, and the other permits the players to break the sky boundary, escaping not only enemy fire but damage from the circle, too.</p><p>As demonstrated by livestreamer LazarBeam (thanks, <a href="https://www.slashgear.com/fortnite-cardboard-box-glitch-makes-players-totally-invisible-29614742/">Slashgear</a>), players that hide in a cardboard box and crouch whilst aiming the harpoon gun will remain invisible to opposing players.</p><p>Interestingly you can't use any other firearm - they'll be visible even if you're not - and canny players have already learned to be cautious of open cardboard boxes.  </p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-these-latest-fortnite-glitches-almost-guarantee-a-win">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-these-latest-fortnite-glitches-almost-guarantee-a-win</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088236</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 16:34:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Yes, Netflix's Castlevania is coming back for a fourth season</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-15-10/-1585491010492.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088230.jpg" alt=""/><p>Netflix's animated Castlevania series is returning for a fourth season.</p><p>Making the announcement on the NXOnNetflix Twitter account - "Netflix's home of all things geek" - fans were encouraged to reply with clap emojis to summon Sir Mirror with news of the show. Naturally, they obliged, and just nine minutes later, this update appeared: </p><p>I know: it doesn't tell us much, does it? We'll have to wait for more concrete details but for now, all we can confirm for sure is that "season four is coming".</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-yes-netflixs-castlevania-is-coming-back-for-a-fourth-season">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-yes-netflixs-castlevania-is-coming-back-for-a-fourth-season</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088230</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 14:44:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>New Horizon Zero Dawn comic series will release later this year</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-13-32/-1585485119693.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088224.jpg" alt=""/><p>Titan Comics has confirmed it's launching a new comic series based upon Horizon Zero Dawn.</p><p>As spotted by our friends at <a href="https://www.videogameschronicle.com/news/horizon-zero-dawn-comic-book-series-launching-summer-2020/">VGC</a>, the comic book series has been co-created by Anne Toole - who is one of the game's original writers - with artwork from Ann Maulina. The story will take us beyond the events of the game.</p><p>"Talanah, a strong and determined hunter, struggles to find purpose after her trusted friend Aloy disappears," Titan <a href="https://www.comixology.com/Horizon-Zero-Dawn-1/digital-comic/853222">explains</a>. "When a mysterious threat emerges in the wilds, she sets out to hunt and to defeat it, only to learn that a whole new breed of killer machines stalk the land!"</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-new-horizon-zero-dawn-comic-series-will-release-later-this-year">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-new-horizon-zero-dawn-comic-series-will-release-later-this-year</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088224</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 13:23:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>
	<item>
		<title>&quot;Upgraded&quot; Nier Replicant announced for PC, PS4 and Xbox One</title>
		<description><![CDATA[<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2020/articles/2020-03-29-12-56/-1585482962417.jpg/EG11/resize/300x-1/format/jpg/2088220.jpg" alt=""/><p>Square Enix has confirmed it is bringing an "upgraded" version of Nier Replicant to PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One.</p><p>The remake of the decade-old action RPG was <a href="https://www.jp.square-enix.com/nierreplicantv1p2/">announced earlier today</a> on a livestream celebrating the game's tenth anniversary. Whilst Platinum Games isn't involved in the upgrade - that's being led by Toylogic - Takahisa Taura, who worked as the senior game designer on Nier: Automata, is reportedly involved (thanks, <a href="https://www.siliconera.com/nier-reincarnation-announced-for-smartphones/">Siliconera</a>).</p><p>"NieR Replicant ver.1.22474487139..., an upgraded version of the original, is now in development for PS4, Xbox One and Steam!" the developer said via the official Nier Twitter account. "Enter an apocalyptic world as you play as a brother on a quest to cure his sister of a deadly disease in this unique action RPG."</p><p><a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-upgraded-nier-replicant-announced-for-pc-ps4-and-xbox-one">Read more</a></p>]]></description>
		<link>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2020-03-29-upgraded-nier-replicant-announced-for-pc-ps4-and-xbox-one</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2088220</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:53:00 +0100</pubDate>	</item>

</channel>
</rss>		